<root>

<Question QID="Q1" QCATEGORY="Beauty and Style" QDATE="2010-06-05 09:21:29" QUSERID="U1" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Massage oil</QSubject>
	<QBody>Where I can buy good oil for massage?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q1_C1" CUSERID="U2" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Massage oil</CSubject>
		<CBody>I've done it once at the Sharq Village &amp; Spa ... It's great

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q1_C2" CUSERID="U1" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Massage oil</CSubject>
		<CBody>Dear, All!
Please read question before you are writing answer! i wasn`t asking where I can do massage!!!
I asked about oil!

As for second answer - I`m searching oil for body massage. Bought one in Canterpoint, there is a small shop near sports shop, and that oil has nice smell, but! It`s not for making massage to anyone! </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q1_C3" CUSERID="U1" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Massage oil</CSubject>
		<CBody>Again...I`m happy for you that you have oil?!
Did you read my question?! I have a lots of things, but I`m not writing here about it!!!
Don`t be stupid, people, read before you write something!!!
I have question, need answer directly to this question, not your empty answers about nothing!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q1_C4" CUSERID="U3" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Massage oil</CSubject>
		<CBody>You might be able to find Body Massage Oil in Body Shop at Landmark or City Centre, and if they do have it there, its guaranteed to be good for massage, as some places sell duplicates, so watch out as this could cause allergies to the skin. Good Luck !</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q1_C5" CUSERID="U4" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Massage oil</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hi. According to your body nature in your picture!!!!!!!!
I advise you to use car oil any type forever like my car. It is helpfull to maintaine your body brigthness.


</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q1_C6" CUSERID="U4" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Massage oil</CSubject>
		<CBody>Oh SORRY. Iam stupied also, your ?WHERE?
My answer is in PETROL STATIONS.........</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q2" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2012-01-21 11:02:29" QUSERID="U5" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Can i exptend my family visit visa after 6 month??</QSubject>
	<QBody>Dear Members,
I have my wife in qatar on family visit visa, now it's gonna over 6 months, can i get more 2/3 months visa?? what is the procedure??
pls inform.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q2_C1" CUSERID="U5" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Can i exptend my family visit visa after 6 month??</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks, but where can i get english format visa extension form??
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q3" QCATEGORY="Electronics" QDATE="2011-04-24 18:09:28" QUSERID="U6" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Which is better from your experience  Nokia N8 or Iphone 4?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Which is better from your experience  Nokia N8 or Iphone 4?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q3_C1" CUSERID="U7" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which is better from your experience  Nokia N8 or...</CSubject>
		<CBody>iphone 4</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q4" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2008-11-19 14:32:05" QUSERID="U8" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>how to extend the visit visa after 6 months and how long period?</QSubject>
	<QBody>want to extend the visit visa. What are the procedures and how long i get the extension. thanks for the answers...</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q4_C1" CUSERID="U9" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how to extend the visit visa after 6 months and how...</CSubject>
		<CBody>chief tailor i think he already get yuor message.... once is enough.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q5" QCATEGORY="Sightseeing and Tourist attractions" QDATE="2010-01-25 06:57:04" QUSERID="U10" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>how can my boyfriend get me and our baby son a visit visa there?</QSubject>
	<QBody>How can my boyfriend who currently works for a government office there get me and our baby a visit visa? How long can we stay there in doha and can we also get married there as well? Can we stay together in his house there? Can you give us advice and the steps to take for getting visa and requirements for marriage there in Qatar? It will be greatly appreciated.Thanks in advance</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q5_C1" CUSERID="U11" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can my boyfriend get me and our baby son a visit...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Boyfriend cant. But as a husband he can apply for visit visa for both of you.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q5_C2" CUSERID="U12" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can my boyfriend get me and our baby son a visit...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yep Boyfriend cannot sponsor you but if he becomes your husband then he can..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q5_C3" CUSERID="U13" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can my boyfriend get me and our baby son a visit...</CSubject>
		<CBody>As far as i know you need to show a proof as a marriage certificate when applying as you have to show your proof of relationship.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q5_C4" CUSERID="U14" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can my boyfriend get me and our baby son a visit...</CSubject>
		<CBody>your nationality plays a major role here. coz there r certain citizenships who can get on arrival visas just from the airport on arrival. if u r from one of those countries, u don't have any problem. just buy the tickets, come down here, get the visa from the airport on arrival BUT YOUR CITIZENSHIP......!!!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q5_C5" CUSERID="U10" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can my boyfriend get me and our baby son a visit...</CSubject>
		<CBody>we want to get married there in Qatar once we arrive there..its this possible?  I was told that he can apply for visit visa for me and our son.. He wants us to get married in Qatar</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q5_C6" CUSERID="U15" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can my boyfriend get me and our baby son a visit...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Dear,

Why dont you let your boy friend arrange the things for you if he really wants to marry you here. The process would be long and lots of documentations needed.

I have a friend who got married here (no child) lots of documentation needed and takes long time to get their marriage certificate issued and therefore she had to fly back to her home country waiting for the attestation of the marriage certificate.

Once it is done, then waiting for family visa to be processed.  So get yourself ready for all the process. Good luck for your wedding.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q5_C7" CUSERID="U10" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can my boyfriend get me and our baby son a visit...</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks for your answers but I really would like some help on this. We want to get married in Qatar. The fact that we are getting married there is it not proof enough for Qatari officials to know that we will be legal and enough requirement for us to stay with my fiance in his house? We were supposed to get married here in the Philippines but he didn't have time for us to set the wedding here..Thanks again!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q5_C8" CUSERID="U16" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can my boyfriend get me and our baby son a visit...</CSubject>
		<CBody>much easier to get a civil married first then apply for the visa,this way you can stay with him legally with no worries at all</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q6" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2009-04-07 23:02:40" QUSERID="U17" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Is it cheaper to buy new clothes in Qatar than pay to transport them over from the UK?</QSubject>
	<QBody>I begin employment in Qatar Aug 09 and have just been quoted 1000 to have them flown over. Is it worth the hassle of customs or should i buy new? How do prices compare UK Next with Qatar Next?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q6_C1" CUSERID="U18" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Is it cheaper to buy new clothes in Qatar than pay to...</CSubject>
		<CBody>since u specifically about NEXT then the prices r the same...except that here u dont get EVERYTHING u find over in the UK but we do have most of the British stores.We have Debanhams,M&amp;S,BHS and Next.But over all 1000 is way to much to pay....depending on how much clothes you have .....or need...i would humbly suggest that u evaluate yr clothes because u know the prices, u alone will be able to judge if the money will buy u what u decide to leave behind...
Good luck</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q6_C2" CUSERID="U19" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Is it cheaper to buy new clothes in Qatar than pay to...</CSubject>
		<CBody>I'm kinda particular about and partial to my clothing so I brought mine. The choices here are not infinite and there isn't the catelog shopping available either.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q6_C3" CUSERID="U20" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Is it cheaper to buy new clothes in Qatar than pay to...</CSubject>
		<CBody>If you already have clothes then it's infinitely cheaper to bring them than to buy more!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q6_C4" CUSERID="U21" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Is it cheaper to buy new clothes in Qatar than pay to...</CSubject>
		<CBody>I would just want to reiterate that prices are MUCH higher here. For example yesterday in M&amp;S looked at a pair of trousers, UK price 29.50, Qatar price 200QR, which means about 38 sterling at the current rates. Next I have found to be even worse than this. At another shop bought my son some Clarks sandles costing 245QR which would have been 30 in the UK. Talk about mark up ! I would also say that the range of clothing to the average UK taste is quite limited. As soon as you go outside of the UK shops you can run into some rather ornate clothing. The quality can be questionable aswell. Not sure how the higher end international shops compare. I am currently counting down the days til I go back to the UK in the summer and hit the summer sales ! Planning on going with empty cases and coming back with rather full ones LOL.  </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q7" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2010-04-28 05:57:26" QUSERID="U22" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="Yes">
	<QSubject>Can we resign from the job??</QSubject>
	<QBody>My employer have recruited me as a Business Development Executive in a Labor Visa.I am put on a Impossible task.I want to resign from the Job.Can I do that??</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q7_C1" CUSERID="U23" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Unsure">
		<CSubject>have u signed any contract?</CSubject>
		<CBody>have u signed any contract? if u have, check what is stipulated there.. sometimes, employers require the employee to pay a certain amount of fee if he/she resigns before the probationary period, but you didn't mention how long you've been working with the company..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q7_C2" CUSERID="U24" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>yes, everbody has the right to resign...</CSubject>
		<CBody>the problem is...expenses</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q7_C3" CUSERID="U25" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>like getting banned for 2</CSubject>
		<CBody>like getting banned for 2 years&gt; Is that right?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q7_C4" CUSERID="U26" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>you can resign and go back</CSubject>
		<CBody>you can resign and go back</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q8" QCATEGORY="Cars" QDATE="2009-10-21 08:23:47" QUSERID="U27" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>anyone knows where the best to sell or trade cars here in Doha?</QSubject>
	<QBody>i was thinking of trading or selling my car. in case i want to trade it, where is the best trading company? as well as to where to sell it?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q8_C1" CUSERID="U12" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: anyone knows where the best to sell or trade cars...</CSubject>
		<CBody>BEst Place is Qatarliving ofcourse</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q8_C2" CUSERID="U28" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: anyone knows where the best to sell or trade cars...</CSubject>
		<CBody>u r already in the best place ... advertize here in QL </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q8_C3" CUSERID="U29" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: anyone knows where the best to sell or trade cars...</CSubject>
		<CBody>it might take awhile to sell a dodge car nowadays and if you are looking for a best sell place i don't suggest you to park your car in one of those car shops at salwa roads, it take awhile to be noticed, so  your best bet to find car showrooms inside doha or add your car at http://qatarsale.com by contacting them and they will do the rest</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q8_C4" CUSERID="U30" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: anyone knows where the best to sell or trade cars...</CSubject>
		<CBody>try these sites, www dot qatarsale dot com and www dot qatarcl dot com...good luck</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q8_C5" CUSERID="U31" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: anyone knows where the best to sell or trade cars...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Approach Oasis Used Cars.. they are the best.

Location near Crazy signal

dial 111 to get the contact number.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q8_C6" CUSERID="U32" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: anyone knows where the best to sell or trade cars...</CSubject>
		<CBody>salwa road has a lot of cars showrooms also.

let me tell you something , if you like adventures just go to Industrial Area - Street No. 10 , on thursdays and fridays :) , you will find your self in Cars Souq

alot of cars , alot of people :) .. but if u go there and you was upset .. its not my fault :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q8_C7" CUSERID="U33" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: anyone knows where the best to sell or trade cars...</CSubject>
		<CBody>which car do you have?</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q9" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2011-01-06 21:28:29" QUSERID="U34" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>my doubt </QSubject>
	<QBody>I would like to know some information from you all .
Suppose someone came here under visit visa and extended it up to six month. Then after six month he went, my doubt is that, how many moths should he wait to come here again after. Can he come here again within one month under a new visit visa?   
</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q9_C1" CUSERID="U34" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>twinkle twinkle little star</CSubject>
		<CBody>come on all just clear out my doubt </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q9_C2" CUSERID="U35" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>the person</CSubject>
		<CBody>should have been under family sponsorship. thats the only visa i think which is extensible upto 6 months. Anyways, the person has to wait 3 months to come back.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q9_C3" CUSERID="U36" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>After Three Months.</CSubject>
		<CBody>After Three Months.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q9_C4" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Living up to the reputation Bond and others have given me</CSubject>
		<CBody>Moths will not help you being here at all.

They are fluttery creatures that destroy cloth. I doubt any moth will help you at all.

To be puerile though and living up to the persona some have created for me on QL. I will say this, can't answer your question as I don't have a problem with travel as I am English and as much as we are 'hated' by some we can travel anywhere we like. 
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q10" QCATEGORY="Life in Qatar" QDATE="2009-03-24 17:14:20" QUSERID="U38" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="Unsure">
	<QSubject>is there any temple in qatar ...... </QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi, as most indians live in qatar.... is there any temple in qatar.....</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q10_C1" CUSERID="U39" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Unsure">
		<CSubject>RE: is there any temple in qatar ...... </CSubject>
		<CBody>http://www.qatarliving.com/answers/living-in-qatar/any-hindu-temple

write temple on the search at  the right hand side u will find many threads on this topic..............</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q10_C2" CUSERID="U40" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>RE: is there any temple in qatar ...... </CSubject>
		<CBody>Qatar is basically an islamic country and they see asian expats as slaves and nothi8ng more.
So u may see churches here but you wont find temples.
And idol worship is not allowed in islam.
Hence you wont find temples here.
I hope one day qatar changes the attitude of seeing asians as slaves.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q10_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is there any temple in qatar ...... </CSubject>
		<CBody>Shayampsundar.......
You are prejudiced against Qatar............ why not you leave this country if your religious sentiments are being bashed..... as you claim!!
Asians are slave??????????? Are you treating yourself as a leader of again community here.

Beware such statements can lead to your deportation also....... i know you are still a kid ( based on your profile)...... but refrain from unworthy comments...... otherwise this would lead to problem for your parents who are earning their livelihood here and feeding you!!!
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q10_C4" CUSERID="U41" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is there any temple in qatar ...... </CSubject>
		<CBody>SHYAM SUNDER....

are they treating u as a slave or do u consider yourself to be a rotten slave....coz i do not think that any one here has bothered to chain ur legs to some shackles here and kept u bonded...u are here just for your some meaningful gains and u are making yourself a slave to the country..like any respect a human being deserves everyone has the freedom to choose to stay or go away from a place he likes or dislikes...so if u do not like the systems here y the hell are u making urself a slave or a DOG over here...get lost man to ur own country and iam sure wherever u go u will definitely treat others as slaves..so cheers</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q10_C5" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is there any temple in qatar ...... </CSubject>
		<CBody>shayampsundar, u have the right to speak out and give ur comment or suggestion but u should respect Qatar or the relegion Islam!by giving comments to ur brother.....
if somebody treated u as slave don't generalized all the locals or Qatari/we all know most indians was lazy and trying hard/they think that they know everything but we know that their really something/talkative and staburn...</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q11" QCATEGORY="Socialising" QDATE="2010-01-12 09:51:34" QUSERID="U42" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Who is the Best Hijacker here in QL?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Please Comment :)

</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q11_C1" CUSERID="U42" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>lol</CSubject>
		<CBody>lol Darude
_______________________

'' Live for Nothing or Die for Something ''
_______________________</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q11_C2" CUSERID="U42" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>lol</CSubject>
		<CBody>lol Darude
_______________________

'' Live for Nothing or Die for Something ''
_______________________</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q11_C3" CUSERID="U42" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>lol</CSubject>
		<CBody>lol Darude
_______________________

'' Live for Nothing or Die for Something ''
_______________________</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q12" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2010-09-08 19:16:32" QUSERID="U43" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>when is Eid?</QSubject>
	<QBody>any news?

i heard dubai is having eid tomorrow.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q12_C1" CUSERID="U44" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>EID</CSubject>
		<CBody>is on Friday</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q12_C2" CUSERID="U45" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>EID MUBARAK to all the muslim</CSubject>
		<CBody>EID MUBARAK to all the muslim fellow...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q12_C3" CUSERID="U46" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>ok thanks for info... happy</CSubject>
		<CBody>ok thanks for info... happy EID!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q12_C4" CUSERID="U47" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>well in my experience....when</CSubject>
		<CBody>well in my experience....when the month of Shabaan is 29 then Ramadan is def 30 and vice versa.....</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q12_C5" CUSERID="U48" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>http://translate.goo...</CSubject>
		<CBody>http://translate.google.com/translate?hl=en&amp;sl=ar&amp;u=http://www.aljazeera.net/&amp;ei=msKHTK7YNY-ycbfF0J4I&amp;sa=X&amp;oi=translate&amp;ct=result&amp;resnum=1&amp;ved=0CCcQ7gEwAA&amp;prev=/search%3Fq%3Dwww.%2Baljazeera.net%26hl%3Den%26safe%3Dactive</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q13" QCATEGORY="Life in Qatar" QDATE="2011-03-23 18:55:17" QUSERID="U49" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="Unsure">
	<QSubject>urgent.. pls reply..</QSubject>
	<QBody>is there near hamad health center rouda aria{near church}?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q13_C1" CUSERID="U50" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Unsure">
		<CSubject>RE: urgent.. pls reply..</CSubject>
		<CBody>Your question is not clear and you need urgent reply ? 
Next to impossible, pls wait until next world cup football in 2022 new constructions are coming up in Qatar, someone will try to answer you.  </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q13_C2" CUSERID="U51" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>RE: urgent.. pls reply..</CSubject>
		<CBody>Seems you are trying to find out whether any health centre in Al Rawda area,

The nearest one I belive in Airport Health centre, go there and ask, then they will guide you.

Airport Health centre is on the Airport Road near DHL</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q13_C3" CUSERID="U49" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: urgent.. pls reply..</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks for you guys reply</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q14" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2009-03-19 10:55:40" QUSERID="U52" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Infiniti G 35 vs. Lexus IS 300 opinions??</QSubject>
	<QBody>i'm doing some new car shopping and seeking your valubale opinions .. 
i have short listed the cars to Infiniti G 35 and Lexus Is 300 .. any experinces with these 2 cars??
asking about .. maintaining the car not only purchasing it .. after sales services??</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q14_C1" CUSERID="U53" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Lexus is better.</CSubject>
		<CBody>Lexus is better. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q14_C2" CUSERID="U53" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>If you can afford the IS F.</CSubject>
		<CBody>If you can afford the IS F. There is nothing like it. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q14_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>infiniti G35 anytime...</CSubject>
		<CBody>infiniti G35 anytime...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q14_C4" CUSERID="U54" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>IS 300</CSubject>
		<CBody>Take it from me i have rode on both cars before, both are luxurious, both have fast acclerations and both looking pretty nice. Lexus IS 300 has more functions in it and doesnt need much of a modification since it already looks hot as stock but Infinity G35 can be modified nicely to be just as mean as Lexus. So the choice is yours. Good Luck</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q14_C5" CUSERID="U55" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>If lexus - than hybrid. It's</CSubject>
		<CBody>If &lt;a href="http://autoya.info/lexus_rx450h_test_review/"&gt;lexus&lt;/a&gt; - than hybrid. It's much moderner!!! Or wait until the new one with updated options</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q15" QCATEGORY="Socialising" QDATE="2009-11-27 17:53:12" QUSERID="U56" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>anyone interested in private pilot training </QSubject>
	<QBody>I was wondering if their is any interest in getting private pilots licence in Qatar?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q15_C1" CUSERID="U57" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>lol</CSubject>
		<CBody>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; lol&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;a href="http://tinypic.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i36.tinypic.com/2rcyhwg.jpg" border="0" alt="Image and video hosting </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q16" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2008-09-03 16:31:18" QUSERID="U23" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="Unsure">
	<QSubject>bye bye time.. almost</QSubject>
	<QBody>it's 4:30 pm,.. almost time for me to go home...it had been an interesting QL day today...hope to see everyone again tomorrow,. hopefully, there's not much traffic so travelling home should be a breeze.... good evening to y'all!</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q16_C1" CUSERID="U23" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>lol MD.....</CSubject>
		<CBody>lol MD.....</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q17" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2010-02-08 14:36:51" QUSERID="U58" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>rolex watch</QSubject>
	<QBody>I have a rolex oyster perpetual watch day-date( gift).I don't know what happened to it..it just stops when i don't use it after 4 hours-more or less then when i adjust it,it moves.do anyone have an idea where I can have it checked?thanks!</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q17_C1" CUSERID="U59" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: rolex watch</CSubject>
		<CBody>Go to 51 East (either in City Centre or in Al Maha near Jarir). They are the agents of Rolex and will have technicians.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q17_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: rolex watch</CSubject>
		<CBody>as aby said these are motion watches......</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q17_C3" CUSERID="U60" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: rolex watch</CSubject>
		<CBody>Rolex agent is Modern home, u must take advice from them, according to advice u have to take dession. Secundly your watch is not aut.

Best of luck.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q17_C4" CUSERID="U61" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: rolex watch</CSubject>
		<CBody>This is a common finding when first starting to use a rolex...i panicked when i first got mine and took it back to the dealer as it stopped as i took it off over night the first time i got it...wear it on for a few days then it wont stop if u leave it overnight but it would stop if u leave it for a couple of days though...enjoy it</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q17_C5" CUSERID="U62" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: rolex watch</CSubject>
		<CBody>&lt;P&gt;Im a fan of designer watches,I usually buy rolex,omega,and other luxury watches at http://www.cheap-rolex-shop.com/ http://www.cheaprolexshop.com/ http://www.buycheaprolexwatches.net/ my love watch shops offer the excellent quality and decent price,if youre willing to,you can visit them.&lt;/P&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q18" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2006-11-08 11:33:10" QUSERID="U63" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>body massage</QSubject>
	<QBody>hi there, i can see a lot of massage center here, but i dont which one is better. can someone help me which massage center is good...and how much will it cost me? thanks</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C1" CUSERID="U64" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>and why choose a </CSubject>
		<CBody>PHILIPPINO lady for a massage?? </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C2" CUSERID="U65" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I enjoy the Marriott Spa</CSubject>
		<CBody>I enjoy the Marriott Spa massage a lot. and often go to Ritz Carleton


In the Cookies of Life, FRIENDS are the Chocolate Chips

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C3" CUSERID="U66" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Hi</CSubject>
		<CBody>So you are looking for a message !!! hmmmm i dont recommend any one of them, i went once and i was going to xxxxx with that semi guy, they all are shemales belive me, so if u r looking for that go ahead otherwise there is the only one who is the decent at al saad street, it is after al saad plaza if you are coming from the new traffic light near the BMW, it is called kotakel something like that.

Good luck</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C4" CUSERID="U67" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>we share similar interests.</CSubject>
		<CBody>good facial centres/spas,try marriott or ritz, they have a lovely spa, but expensive.
a new place opened up opp city centre, its called bio something.they too specialise in the same stuff.again expensive.

lady siam centre near toys r us, alsadd area, is good too.they specialise in thai massages and stuff and their facial is really nice and soothing. had it long time back, but communiacting with them is difficult as they speak only thai and broken english.

massage, you can try chinese reflexology massage at ramada, that good too, also the kottakal massage centre in muntaza area, cheap and good for body pains and stuff.both are priced at aprox 100qrs.

almost all saloons do facials and some have real extensive range of facials.u need to try out the places to get a feel of it.

i just saw your profile, you sound so much like me, except the coke and margarita part.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C5" CUSERID="U68" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>LADY MESSAGE</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hi all is there any Phillipino lady makes Good message in Home either for men or for women .. Kindly Send mail to  killer_mllr@yahoo.com with the charges to be mentioned also..
  thanks ..................</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C6" CUSERID="U11" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>message???</CSubject>
		<CBody>&lt;p&gt;every one can make message just pick the damn cell phone and start sendin text or sms or message what ever you call BUT MASSAGE THAT YOU ONLY GET IN JAIL FROM FEMALE INSPECTORS WITH A 10FOOT LONG STICK
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;nbsp;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
[img_assist|nid=73057|title=.|desc=|link=none|align=left|width=|height=0]
&lt;/p&gt;
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C7" CUSERID="U69" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>is this true</CSubject>
		<CBody>is this true....</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C8" CUSERID="U69" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>so where did u reach</CSubject>
		<CBody>any luck  ??</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C9" CUSERID="U70" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Lady Siam</CSubject>
		<CBody>The massage itself is ok, not excellent, but ok. The overall experience is not the best - can never reach them on the phone, the receptionist is not very friendly, not punctual. Another words if you are looking for the experience, this is not the place to go. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C10" CUSERID="U71" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>philippino massage</CSubject>
		<CBody>any body know philippino masseure in doha kindly tel me  they r the best in giving massage or email me
philip.game@hotmail.com
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C11" CUSERID="U72" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Hi qatar127 </CSubject>
		<CBody>Which one is that xxxx place so i keep away frm there as i go offen checking out massage center.

so lt me know were did u get xxxx massage which cenetr

cheers !!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C12" CUSERID="U73" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Lady Siam Massage </CSubject>
		<CBody>I have been a member for the last 8 years.
It is the perfect place for me and highly recommended.
It is always fully booked but schedule yourself one week in advance you'll get one!
There are Gel nail services as well.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C13" CUSERID="U63" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>hay guys</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks , i guess i  wil try the lady shiam, and the bio bil,hhehehe

hmmm what else is new to try here in doha? </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C14" CUSERID="U74" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Hi Gringer,
Ask for Belen at</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hi Gringer,

Ask for Belen at Bio Bil ... she's amazing!! Have fun!!

MC</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C15" CUSERID="U67" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>u wud get only body</CSubject>
		<CBody>u wud get only body massage.............any other massage will be going on inside your head.the place and the person doing your massage....well work your imagination.
wont that be fun and ultra relaxing.


happy heart
drive safe cos someone is waiting for u at home</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C16" CUSERID="U75" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Ladies Siam Massage ...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Recommended that place ... (owned by my thai girlfriend). Their facial are very good and their aromatherapy alot better than Marriot massage. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C17" CUSERID="U76" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>professional massage</CSubject>
		<CBody>I like professional sport massage, specialy after a fitness session, and the masseur at ramada is good; ok also the indian kotakel, the philipino on najima I found depressing and not clean (male section at least).And, as far as I know, there are always masseur for men and masseuse for ladied, this to avoid expectations. Anybody tried the british massage therapist (his ads chilloutnow in QL)  ?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C18" CUSERID="U77" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>just got interested only</CSubject>
		<CBody>how much the charged for the massage at the back only???...not a whole body massage....if there's any...where is that place to be???...thanks</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q18_C19" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I have to say it!!!!!</CSubject>
		<CBody>"This IZ Chief Inspector Clouseau speaking on the pheaun. ... Do you have a massage for me?"

In honor of Peter Sellers

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VnLhvMStUWU</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q19" QCATEGORY="Family Life in Qatar" QDATE="2012-04-10 20:23:21" QUSERID="U78" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Giving a birth in qatar</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi all,

My wife is nearly to give birth and i am wondering which is the best clinic/hospital in qatar,

Some people are considering that hamad is the best other al ahly other clinic al doha ...

Please can you share with us your idea and experience and give us advice.

Thanks in advance</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q19_C1" CUSERID="U79" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>even if you go to al ahli</CSubject>
		<CBody>even if you go to al ahli after delivery you will be referred to hamad for further proceedings...birth certificate, immunization etc..better go to hamad inshallah everything will be fine...to go to ahli is to simply increase your expenses...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q19_C2" CUSERID="U80" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Al Ahli is the best if u have</CSubject>
		<CBody>Al Ahli is the best if u have insurance. I just delivered 6 months back there and was well taken care of. Hamad has limited number of beds in the labour room and some times u have to wait your turn!!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q19_C3" CUSERID="U81" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Best is Doha clinc hospital</CSubject>
		<CBody>Best is Doha clinc hospital and Dr Maha yehia Mohmoud best gynac
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q19_C4" CUSERID="U78" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>As i understand Hamad is a</CSubject>
		<CBody>As i understand Hamad is a government hospital, and Doha clinic is private,
is that right?

and if so, is it always private better than government?
in concerning caring and experience of doctors, right?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q19_C5" CUSERID="U82" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>you will only pay 100 QR per</CSubject>
		<CBody>you will only pay 100 QR per day in hamad.. that's all.. everything is free.. even if C-section is going to be performed only room charge 100 QR/day is going to be paid by the patient.. the shorter she stays in hamad the cheaper it gets...my wife delivered our third baby in 2010 in hamad... now even if i have AXA insurance i will still consider hamad when my wife delivers our next baby in 3 weeks from now.. that is because i am very much satisfied with hamad...best service at lowest cost...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q19_C6" CUSERID="U82" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>hamad hosp will charge 200 QR</CSubject>
		<CBody>hamad hosp will charge 200 QR per day for visit visa pregnant women who will deliver their babies...check hamad women's hospital for more info...</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q20" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2009-03-20 16:04:13" QUSERID="U83" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="No">
	<QSubject>Qatar Airways Cabin Crew</QSubject>
	<QBody>If i wanted to apply for Qatar Airways as Cabin Crew, would they let me sponsor my son? </QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q20_C1" CUSERID="U84" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>no they wont.
Aana free,</CSubject>
		<CBody>no they wont.

Aana free, jaana free,
Pakde gaye tho khana free.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q20_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>Well</CSubject>
		<CBody>i think they are not  hiring the married females... its there policy ... And by chance if you will be selected.. they will not sponsor your son....

Cheers !!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q20_C3" CUSERID="U83" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>i'm</CSubject>
		<CBody>i'm not married. single mom.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q20_C4" CUSERID="U85" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>its not a problem for you to</CSubject>
		<CBody>its not a problem for you to join but sponsoring your son is definitely no no.......
and by the way....they do recruit married females....FYI</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q20_C5" CUSERID="U86" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>In qatar You can ONLY</CSubject>
		<CBody>In qatar You can ONLY sponsor Your family if you work in Government :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q21" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2009-12-28 07:54:50" QUSERID="U37" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>ZAGU In DOHA?</QSubject>
	<QBody>TO all Filipinos here in DOHA.

Would  you like to have the ZAGU ( black pearl shake) here in DOHA?

Just "YES" or "NO" Please.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C1" CUSERID="U87" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>set-up a store to open on</CSubject>
		<CBody>set-up a store to open on each and every mall,

1. City Center
2. Villagio
3. Hyatt Plaza
4. Landmark
5. The Mall
6. Centrepoint
7. Lulu Hypermarket

you may also consider setting-up stores in
1. Souq Waqif
2. Souq Asiery (Pilipino Souq)

&lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;How far you go in life depends on you being tender with the young, compassionate with the aged, tolerant of the weak. Someday you will have been all of these.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C2" CUSERID="U88" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Oh my Yhes!!!! :)</CSubject>
		<CBody>Oh my Yhes!!!! :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C3" CUSERID="U88" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Although I love Quickly</CSubject>
		<CBody>Although I love Quickly better... :(</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C4" CUSERID="U89" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>so where is zagu now?</CSubject>
		<CBody>so where is zagu now?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C5" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RefinedSoul sorry to say u</CSubject>
		<CBody>RefinedSoul sorry to say u dont have one </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C6" CUSERID="U90" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>bigger n longer 4 u, </CSubject>
		<CBody> bigger n longer 4 u, would u try!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C7" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Yes Chinx,,</CSubject>
		<CBody>We are on the process of registration by the way..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C8" CUSERID="U91" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>ITS A BIG</CSubject>
		<CBody>ITS A BIG YESSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS............. ;)


temper is something u cant get rid of... by loosing it...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C9" CUSERID="U92" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Wish you more success.</CSubject>
		<CBody>@ Denis Reyes:

Looking forward that your business will prosper.  We'll be waiting this to happen.
 
Would you be kind enough to give us inputs where how do we get started when putting up business here in Qatar?

Believe!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C10" CUSERID="U11" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>what is</CSubject>
		<CBody>Zagu??
what does it look like.
&lt;img src="http://www.qatarliving.com/files/images/Da.gif"&gt;

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C11" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>YESSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS</CSubject>
		<CBody>YESSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C12" CUSERID="U93" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>yep!love it...are u planning</CSubject>
		<CBody>yep!love it...are u planning to put up a zagu business here?;)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q21_C13" CUSERID="U92" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Isn't it a food franchise in</CSubject>
		<CBody>Isn't it a food franchise in Philippines? The franchise owner would be happy to know about your idea but I believe there are some business issues to hurdle first when franchising in foreign countries.

Starting a ZAGU concept here wither franchise or personal is feasible. Guts and understanding the government business operations in Qatar are essentials. Customer satisfaction and profitability come next.

For sure, we are your "SUKI" regular customers. Our family love to hear, we got one "Orig'l PINOY!" in DOHA.  </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q22" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2009-01-17 01:58:46" QUSERID="U94" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Where can i buy globe roam sim here in qatar?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Can anyone tell me where can i buy globe roaming sim? thanks! if your selling globe roaming sim.. you can call me at +9746057424.. thnx! </QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C1" CUSERID="U95" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>vivo bonito, did you just</CSubject>
		<CBody>vivo bonito, did you just cut and paste that from the Globe Website? :D LOL

Mine was my own words. bec. i used to work with SMART :p</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C2" CUSERID="U96" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>nkotb... i am not working to</CSubject>
		<CBody>nkotb... i am not working to any either of the smart or globe.. and that was my opinion when i bought one family sim pack... to where, at my disappointments.. were not all true upon on the run...(sigh)hell network, a misguiding false adverts ...;,,

&lt;a href="http://s185.photobucket.com/albums/x25/casabella1434/?action=view&amp;current=sheep.gif" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i185.photobucket.com/albums/x25/casabella1434/sheep.gif" border="0" alt="Photobucket"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
~~Life's Cycle~~~ </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C3" CUSERID="U95" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>VB, i didnt say you are</CSubject>
		<CBody>VB, i didnt say you are working with smart or globe. Geesh! I just meant, your first post, i bet it came from the website of globe and you just cut and paste it here in QL. LOL</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C4" CUSERID="U96" CGOLD="Not English" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>labo mo naman mang-amoy kung</CSubject>
		<CBody>labo mo naman mang-amoy kung nagbabasa... 

GLOBE FAMILY SIM PACK comes with 1PC OFW PREACTIVATED ROAMING SIM and 2PCS FAMILY SIM sold at PHP120.00 only available at designated retail outlets in the Philippines. u would easily find it while processing some of ur papers at POEA Ortigas.

dito ako nakabili ng SIMPACK mismo sa loob ng POEA habang antay ng tawag ng number ko.. dami kaya walk-in sellers sa loob...


&lt;a href="http://s185.photobucket.com/albums/x25/casabella1434/?action=view&amp;current=sheep.gif" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i185.photobucket.com/albums/x25/casabella1434/sheep.gif" border="0" alt="Photobucket"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
~~Life's Cycle~~~ </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C5" CUSERID="U97" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>at the souq.... you mean</CSubject>
		<CBody>at the souq.... you mean globe users in the phils. can call our globe roaming here? seriously? what's the rate per minute?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C6" CUSERID="U95" CGOLD="Not English" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Hina naman ng catsup ng</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hina naman ng catsup ng ibang tao talaga oo! WATIBER!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C7" CUSERID="U94" CGOLD="Not English" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Eo!!</CSubject>
		<CBody>Wel.. Mga prinds.. tentyu sa mga adbays nyu.. mebi ay'l dyas stek tu smart por naw.. mdameng tentyu! we chat using Ym.. bat it's nat enaf.. ^^ waheheh! tenty por ol yor koments prinds! </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C8" CUSERID="U98" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>i heard that globe's signal is not good here</CSubject>
		<CBody>and besides calling thru roaming will be more expensive. anyway, in the souq ull find sim roaming for smart, dont know about globe

&lt;a href="http://s255.photobucket.com/albums/hh125/kooleeet/?action=view&amp;current=i_l_ve_y.gif" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i255.photobucket.com/albums/hh125/kooleeet/i_l_ve_y.gif" border="0" alt="Photobucket"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C9" CUSERID="U99" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>you can go to filipino souq</CSubject>
		<CBody>you can go to filipino souq you cab get it for QR 25.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C10" CUSERID="U100" CGOLD="Not English" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>ask lang po, mgkano nmn po</CSubject>
		<CBody>ask lang po, mgkano nmn po mgpaelectronic load dun sa souq. ty...

&lt;a href="http://graphics-comment.blogspot.com?c=hugs&amp;n=6"&gt;&lt;img src="http://ZangyGraphics.com/hugs/6.gif" border="0" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://graphics-comment.blogspot.com"&gt;&lt;img src="http://zangygraphics.com/imgs/zangylogo.jpg" border="0" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C11" CUSERID="U94" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>waaaaaaaaaaa!!</CSubject>
		<CBody>i Already checked the kababayan supermarket. but they dont have globe roaming sim there. only smart. i'm using smart now just for temporary. Smart cannot be called but i'm not sure of it. My gf is globe and its too expensive for her to text to my smart because it will cost her 2php every text. Everytime my gf call me it cost her.. 20php per 1min. uhmm.. Maybe I'll try to find globe sim in souq. I hope i could get one there. Globe has a good signal here too. When i arrived here im using globe roaming sim. and its ok but it was been deactivated last thursday because my load dind'nt catch up. ehehe!Thank you!! ill try to check the stores again there or if i cant really find one here.. maybe i'll just ask my friends in phil who are going here in qatar.  Thanks again! btw are you all filipino? ^_^
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C12" CUSERID="U101" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>i didnt see any globe sim in</CSubject>
		<CBody>i didnt see any globe sim in filipino souq... there are lots of smart sim available in souq.. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C13" CUSERID="U95" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>simangot, i suggest your GF</CSubject>
		<CBody>simangot, i suggest your GF switch to smart sim in pinas. I will tell you some encouragement and ideas. And advantages and disadvantages of both Globe and Smart. Here it goes:

With SMART, you dont have to load everyday or every week just to maintain your sim or be activated. you can do SmartLoad or Over The Air Reload once in 3 Months. The sim will be deactivated within 120 days of NO LOAD. 1 Peso text from Pinas to Internatioal Roaming Sim. Smart Signal is also good in Doha. In industrial Area is good, why not in the city. :)

With GLOBE, you have to maintain a LOAD everytime for the rest of your life in abroad. Much Expensive.

With Smart, when activated as Roaming Sim, Pure Text only. While Globe, you can receive/make calls but it's expensive. International Rate Charges Apply. If you happen to buy that Globe OFW Sim, it's a BULL! They said on the TV Commercials that no maintaining balance for 1 year or Forever, i dont remember anymore. It's not True! you still have to reload within 1 month of use.

I guess you are working here in Doha, right? I bet you talk to your GF at night or after work or in the morning. Why don't you buy QTEL Sim from QTEL Offices. It's only 50QR now, i think they still have this Promo going on. Or better yet, there is this internet calls located in Doha. Maybe its in Souq or Industrial Area. 1 minute is to 1QR. Cheaper than using your QTEL SIm to call Pinas for 1.85QR per minute.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C14" CUSERID="U96" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>GLOBE FAMILY SIM PACK comes</CSubject>
		<CBody>GLOBE FAMILY SIM PACK comes with 1PC OFW PREACTIVATED ROAMING SIM and 2PCS FAMILY SIM sold at PHP120.00 only available at designated retail outlets in the Philippines. u would easily find it while processing some of ur papers at POEA Ortigas.

Family Sim can text and call the OFW Sim at a cost of philippine local standard SMS and Calling charges. The OFW sim remains still active even at a zero load balance while abroad provided, however, any of the family sim must use the facility of SMS or calling at a time not exceeding within a month period. Anyhow, anyone of the Family Sim dont have any SMS or calling activity within a month to an OFW SIM, the service shall be automatically deactivated. Likewise, the OFW sim lost its special service capabilities. The OFW SIM will be then regarded as ordinary SIM.

&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q22_C15" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>why stick to Globe? A lots</CSubject>
		<CBody>why stick to Globe? A lots of Smart Roaming SIM is available in Souq Area. Electronic loading is also available there.


EOF0825</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q23" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2011-05-12 12:37:18" QUSERID="U102" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>How is Gulf Driving School?</QSubject>
	<QBody>I want to take a Driving Classes from Gulf Driving School as it is near to my flat. Can anyone suggest me the popularity of this School?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q23_C1" CUSERID="U20" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: How is Gulf Driving School?</CSubject>
		<CBody>It's popular with guys living near your flat.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q23_C2" CUSERID="U103" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: How is Gulf Driving School?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Most of people prefer Karwa driving school. As registration process is swift. I heard from my fellas there is some offerfor  full course, but your enrollment will come after 1 month.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q23_C3" CUSERID="U104" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: How is Gulf Driving School?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Gulf driving school offers the best chance of you getting your licence among all the driving schools. It is popular because of the high success rate. The teaching however is terrible. So if you really want to learn driving, go to some other place. If you just want the licence, you can try gulf driving school</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q24" QCATEGORY="Working in Qatar" QDATE="2009-01-27 13:08:16" QUSERID="U105" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Location of Bosnia</QSubject>
	<QBody>Anybody who knows the location of bosnia near dasman center?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q24_C1" CUSERID="U106" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Location of Bosnia</CSubject>
		<CBody>Bosnia and Herzegovina located : Left from Romania, Right from Rome, little Down from Hungary and little up from Bulgaria. Not far from Black see.   
I think its enough for u. 
Thank u </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q24_C2" CUSERID="U105" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Location of Bosnia</CSubject>
		<CBody>What i mean is bosnia embassy</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q24_C3" CUSERID="U107" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Location of Bosnia</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hello...
I can show you on map....milady...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q24_C4" CUSERID="U108" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Location of Bosnia</CSubject>
		<CBody>How generous is Alimar...hehehee...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q24_C5" CUSERID="U105" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Location of Bosnia</CSubject>
		<CBody>im looking for embassy of bosnia, somebody called me and said its near dasman center. im going there later this evening</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q24_C6" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Location of Bosnia</CSubject>
		<CBody>hello friend,
Bear in mind that there are more than one Dasman centre in the city...cheeers</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q24_C7" CUSERID="U109" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Location of Bosnia</CSubject>
		<CBody>Bosnian emabssy was on D ring road,but go to 180 and get number,call them and get location.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q25" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2012-02-05 03:40:11" QUSERID="U110" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Walking in Doha</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi

This might be a bit of an odd question but can you walk from the Japanese Embassy or the Kempinski Hotel to City Centre Shopping Centre?  It looks definitely walkable distance-wise but do the roads preclude any chance of walking?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q25_C1" CUSERID="U111" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>noo its very unsafe</CSubject>
		<CBody>U have dodge bullets bombs and air strikes </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q25_C2" CUSERID="U112" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I see a lot of people are</CSubject>
		<CBody>I see a lot of people are walking in City Centre area in the evenings and weekends. They park their cars all around W, Kempinski, and stuff, and just walk.. it's not really safe, as there are no sidewalks in Doha, but as I said, I see many people do it.. Life is unsafe in general.. so.. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q25_C3" CUSERID="U110" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thanks very much.  I once</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks very much.  I once made the mistake before going out to Dubai of assuming I could easily walk across the Sheikh Zayed Road...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q25_C4" CUSERID="U19" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Yes, but only in the</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yes, but only in the winter!
Mandi</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q26" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2008-11-10 11:29:15" QUSERID="U113" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>General tier 1 migrant visa to UK</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi ladies and gentlemen, i would like to know if any one has experience applying for UK visa General Tier 1 that allows u to work in UK. please ur advise is v important.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q26_C1" CUSERID="U114" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I happen to know first</CSubject>
		<CBody>I happen to know first hand..factors such as age, education and earnings for the past 12 mths of the applicant will be alloted 'points' and if he/she meets the minimum points for this visa category then its not a problem at all. You will have to apply from outside the UK for this, even if you are currently residing there under a different visa category.

What do you want to know specifically?


~Live like there's no tommorrow~</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q26_C2" CUSERID="U113" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thanks for your reply Pin,</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks for your reply Pin, have u applied before for this type of visa? i would like to know how easy i can be accepted and how long it takes to know if i will be granted this visa.. please advise</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q26_C3" CUSERID="U114" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>yes, i have been working and</CSubject>
		<CBody>yes, i have been working and living in london for more than 1 year under a highly skilled migrant programme (HSMP) and i subsequently switched to Tier 1 (General).

bear in mind - i got my visa way before the uk recession and jobs were easy to come by. now unemployment is a big issue here. you won't be able to renew the tier 1 visa without a skilled job.

anyways, it is unlawful to reject your application if you :-
1) have met the minimum 75 points 
2) can proof that you meet the required English standard
3) have minimum funds of GBP2800.
4) obviously, you must not have any prior criminal convictions or have previously abused your immigration status(i.e. overstayed on a visa, outstanding fines in uk, etc)

don't bother applying if you don't meet the above. for me, application to approval took 3 weeks, applying from KL, Malaysia.

for precise requirements and how points are calculated, see http://www.ukvisas.gov.uk/en/howtoapply/infs/inf21pbsgeneralmigrant#6375036

good luck.

~Live like there's no tommorrow~</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q26_C4" CUSERID="U113" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>am so lucky to have your advice</CSubject>
		<CBody>i am so lucky to have your advice, knowing that u went through the same procedures before. what do u mean "you won't be able to renew the tier 1 visa without a skilled job". actually i am not renewing, and do they gauge their approval by the required profession on top of the ones u mentioned.
did u validate ur degrees with NARIC, any advice here?
must be the bank statement not older than 7 days or it is fine to be a bit older?
i have applied TOEFLE for more than 5 years ago, do they take this into consideration?
please advise, thanks v much indeed</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q26_C5" CUSERID="U114" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>No probs..</CSubject>
		<CBody>the tier 1 general visa is for 24 months only. to extend your stay beyond 24 months you must renew it. you won't be able to do so without a job.

as far as i know, you must have at least a bachelor's degree and that's how they accept that you are 'highly skilled'. they want ORIGINAL documents, no copies. don't worry they will return these to you.

bank statements - latest 3 months showing minimum of GBP2800 and must be original as well.

TOEFL is accepted, marks must be 110-120 (internet based test). you must also provide the original cert and test scores.


~Live like there's no tommorrow~</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q26_C6" CUSERID="U113" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>one more query</CSubject>
		<CBody>do u think that they accept notarized copy of my certificates and not original ones?
is it possible to get ur email for future correspondence?
thanks so much, you have been v helpful to me</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q26_C7" CUSERID="U113" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>thanks so much for ur reply, </CSubject>
		<CBody>greatly appreciated</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q27" QCATEGORY="Family Life in Qatar" QDATE="2009-08-20 22:23:09" QUSERID="U115" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>can anyone help me!</QSubject>
	<QBody>Can anyone advice me about my kids, can't sleep for whole night.They will start to sleep at 6am</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q27_C1" CUSERID="U116" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: can anyone help me!</CSubject>
		<CBody>I recommend buying them Melatonin. I started using it 3 weeks ago. I get sleepy soon after taking 2 and I have a great sleep. I don't wake up with that lingering tiredness that something like, say, Panadol Night, does. The pharmacy opposite Carrefour in Villagio definitely has it for about QR36 and I'm sure you'll find it at other pharmacies (no prescription needed of course).

Best of luck!  </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q27_C2" CUSERID="U117" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: can anyone help me!</CSubject>
		<CBody>http://www.childdevelopmentinfo.com/health_safety/child_teen_sleep.htm
don't use medication without asking DR.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q27_C3" CUSERID="U118" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: can anyone help me!</CSubject>
		<CBody>Dont let them sleep for a day in the morning.at night they will fall asleep.continue this for a week.they will get used.don't ever change the sheddule time.put them on bed on time.Let them be entertained during day time.and not allow at night.

If they are toddlers they usually dose'nt want to sleep.they try to experience the surroundings.Make them to understand that night is to sleep or rest.Don't use lights which are bright.try not to use or a very mild power.don't encourage them at night to talk/play/have snacks..etc.So they'll feel the night boaring and they automatically go to sleep.

Try some bedtime stories.give them a bed time and never ever change it.Be stricked on the rule.I think it will work out surely.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q27_C4" CUSERID="U119" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: can anyone help me!</CSubject>
		<CBody>addict for playing games on gadgets, is one of the reason also, so it should be limit or qiuet to avoid . 2nd, discipline from a parent is the best way,"mother's knows best"

best regards!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q28" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2009-11-10 13:21:42" QUSERID="U120" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Where can I buy Low Fat/Sugar Free/Sweetner Birtdhay Cake?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi

Where can i buy a made to order cake with lowfat or sweetener used? 

Thanks,

Qaisar</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q28_C1" CUSERID="U121" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can I buy Low Fat/Sugar Free/Sweetner Birtdhay...</CSubject>
		<CBody>U can place an order for accordingly, in local mkt U cant find,
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q28_C2" CUSERID="U122" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can I buy Low Fat/Sugar Free/Sweetner Birtdhay...</CSubject>
		<CBody>bake it at home</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q28_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can I buy Low Fat/Sugar Free/Sweetner Birtdhay...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Go for a water cracker instead. 

Otherwise, the Diet Shop on Salwa Road next to VW and Johnny Rockets sell what you are looking for.  </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q29" QCATEGORY="Sightseeing and Tourist attractions" QDATE="2008-10-30 08:36:14" QUSERID="U123" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Anyone who has a printable map of Doha?</QSubject>
	<QBody>It is very hard to find in the internet, even here in QL I could not find a Doha Map. Anyone who has Doha map that I can print? Or at least an internet link.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q29_C1" CUSERID="U124" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Anyone who has a printable map of Doha?</CSubject>
		<CBody>please use this link  - 'http://www.dohamap.info/map/</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q29_C2" CUSERID="U20" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Anyone who has a printable map of Doha?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Go to any stationery shop and buy one!
There's also a good one in Marhaba</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q29_C3" CUSERID="U125" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Anyone who has a printable map of Doha?</CSubject>
		<CBody>the Qatar guidebook called Marhaba has an excellent map (although it's hard to keep maps here updated as there is always lots of construction and you don't know when the road you used yesterday will close or disappear). The Doha Ritz hotel stocks the same maps for guests, I bet if you went to the Ritz in KL they would have one inter-officed to you! Good luck!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q29_C4" CUSERID="U126" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Anyone who has a printable map of Doha?</CSubject>
		<CBody>got mine from marhaba.... its great!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q29_C5" CUSERID="U127" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Anyone who has a printable map of Doha?</CSubject>
		<CBody>u can download from http://www.explore-qatar.com/downloads/Maps/   ok</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q30" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2012-09-12 08:41:32" QUSERID="U128" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Does anywhere in qatar sell pineapple juice</QSubject>
	<QBody>Searching high and low for pineapple juice not concentrated rubbish can find it anywhere .  Pleaee guys accept this mission </QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q30_C1" CUSERID="U128" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Il tel my wife about that one</CSubject>
		<CBody>Il tel my wife about that one i cant get to grips with advocado</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q30_C2" CUSERID="U129" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>better make it at home :)</CSubject>
		<CBody>better make it at home :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q30_C3" CUSERID="U130" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Buy only this brand "Del</CSubject>
		<CBody>Buy only this brand "Del Monte Pineapple" it's 100% pure and fresh and no artificial flavors. It's stored in a big can. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q30_C4" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>try KABAYAN in souq</CSubject>
		<CBody>try KABAYAN in souq</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q30_C5" CUSERID="U131" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I would recommend Del Monte</CSubject>
		<CBody>I would recommend Del Monte Pineapple juice available in most hypermarket and Kabayan Stores.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q30_C6" CUSERID="U131" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>If not satisfied with Del</CSubject>
		<CBody>If not satisfied with Del Monte, best option is to buy fresh Pineapple and make at home.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q31" QCATEGORY="Socialising" QDATE="2009-01-09 13:37:27" QUSERID="U132" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>North Indian group for families to socialize </QSubject>
	<QBody>there seem to be groups for all communities here. Is there any for north indian families ? If not, then lets make one ? Anybody interested ?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q31_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I am a bachelor so I guess</CSubject>
		<CBody>I am a bachelor so I guess can't be a member, Will contact you next year when I am married.


" when someone annoys you it takes 42 muscles in your face to frown, BUT, it only takes 4 muscles to extend your arm and slap that @&amp;%$%^$$#&amp;!!!!"</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q31_C2" CUSERID="U133" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>good one arrhsa..lol</CSubject>
		<CBody>good one arrhsa..lol</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q31_C3" CUSERID="U39" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>go ahead.....</CSubject>
		<CBody>go ahead.....</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q31_C4" CUSERID="U134" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>for ladies group I m also</CSubject>
		<CBody>for ladies group I m also ready.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q31_C5" CUSERID="U135" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>First we go</CSubject>
		<CBody>Indian group then we go north indian group now we go north indian ladies group - what next - noth indian ladies less then 5 feet 6 inches group?????
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q31_C6" CUSERID="U136" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>North Indian</CSubject>
		<CBody>I uderstand there is one NIA - North Indian Asscoiation, who normaly conducts programs in RAMADA...

haa. i liked the reply from arrhsa.... less than 5'6"

what about left-handers ?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q31_C7" CUSERID="U135" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Yep - left handers too</CSubject>
		<CBody>I was just tryin to say we are all expats here so why keep dividing all the way - eventually we'll all end up where we started - alone with no one to advise!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q31_C8" CUSERID="U137" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>yes I am
 interested</CSubject>
		<CBody>yes I am
 interested</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q32" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2009-02-22 12:36:41" QUSERID="U138" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Prepaid credit card for online purchasing?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Is there any prepaid service, which I can use for online shopping? I dont know what it called, prepaid credit card or prepaid debit card or what? Anyway, Actually I dont want to open a bank account. Im looking something more easy and instant, if I pay cash and they give me online credits for purchasing?  I dont know is it possible or not and how it works. If anybody have some idea about it will be grateful for me.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q32_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Prepaid credit card for online purchasing?</CSubject>
		<CBody>go to jarir bookstore they sell those cards called CashU. but they work on some internet sites. go check it out.
before buying go to cashu.com and check if the site you want buy from has it.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q32_C2" CUSERID="U139" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Prepaid credit card for online purchasing?</CSubject>
		<CBody>I am really looking to find a solution for buying online localy in Qatar or from internet such as Amazoon.com.
I heared that one banke issuing such cards @ 500 QR, and they deduct 50 QR service and you can buy up to 450 QR.
But I didn't try to find that Bank</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q32_C3" CUSERID="U140" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Prepaid credit card for online purchasing?</CSubject>
		<CBody>QNB use to do it .. but now they make it for only CC holders


u can check with THE GROUP

or Doha bank</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q32_C4" CUSERID="U139" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Prepaid credit card for online purchasing?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Using ATM card would be great, but it is not safe. I addition to that who asked this quastion dont have an bank account.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q32_C5" CUSERID="U139" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Prepaid credit card for online purchasing?</CSubject>
		<CBody>If any body can advice QNB and Doha Bank Tel. No. to call them and aske to get better informations and Details</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q33" QCATEGORY="Life in Qatar" QDATE="2012-08-28 12:12:08" QUSERID="U141" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Villa on a budget</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi,

I am new to Qatar and have a budget of 10,000 Qr for a villa.  Children go to Sherborne but don't need to be in it's doorstep.  Can anyone point me in the right direction for this budget please?
Many thanks</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q33_C1" CUSERID="U141" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Great thank you I will get</CSubject>
		<CBody>Great thank you I will get the map out and start hunting. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q33_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Ive been looking for a villa</CSubject>
		<CBody>Ive been looking for a villa for the past 3 weeks , and i know where al the villas are , if ur interested send me a message , i can recommend some good ones ive seen and that are in ur range :) </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q33_C3" CUSERID="U141" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Great can you please tell me</CSubject>
		<CBody>Great can you please tell me how to send private message</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q33_C4" CUSERID="U141" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thank you wil give agent a</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thank you wil give agent a call</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q34" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2009-10-09 04:59:13" QUSERID="U142" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>wedding card designers</QSubject>
	<QBody>Does anybody know any nice wedding card designers from Doha or any company that can do the design and printing of wedding cards?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q34_C1" CUSERID="U143" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: wedding card designers</CSubject>
		<CBody>call this no 3069472</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q34_C2" CUSERID="U142" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: wedding card designers</CSubject>
		<CBody>and where is bin mahmoud street?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q34_C3" CUSERID="U142" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: wedding card designers</CSubject>
		<CBody>thank you.. do u recommend any shops on that street?</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q35" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2009-05-11 19:53:58" QUSERID="U144" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>For the ladies</QSubject>
	<QBody>Please help me....I am looking to buy a wet grinder in Doha.... Can anyone who has purchased one from here give me the Make and Model no..... something small for the table-top and with no other attachments as i have everything else......


</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C1" CUSERID="U145" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I used to know someone</CSubject>
		<CBody>I used to know someone affectionately nicknamed "wet grinder"................Memories :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C2" CUSERID="U146" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Is this one</CSubject>
		<CBody>you Indian call"MIXI"?That is available in all ffc,lulu and dasman centre.Hope it'll help.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C3" CUSERID="U147" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Leelah Mixi..lol is</CSubject>
		<CBody>Leelah Mixi..lol is different from grinder... Mixi/blender  is used to grind and also make powders as well...but in wet grinder...we can make all sort of batters...it can be used only for grinding more quantity..


&lt;a href="http://photobucket.com/images/funny" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i244.photobucket.com/albums/gg12/N-A-T-A-S-J-A/Funny/smile.gif" border="0" alt="smile Pictures, Images and Photos"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C4" CUSERID="U131" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Check in LULU 3 models are</CSubject>
		<CBody>Check in LULU 3 models are available &lt;pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;#160;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;#160;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;#160;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
[img_assist|nid=50852|title=hmm|desc=|link=none|align=left|width=|height=0] 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C5" CUSERID="U148" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Look at FS suddenly trying</CSubject>
		<CBody>Look at FS suddenly trying to show everyone her vast knowledge of the kitchen and its tools. Go learn to cook as good as your mother in law first! :p

Good Fortune always comes knocking at your door...when you are sh*tting in the toilet!! :)
&lt;p&gt;
_[]~&lt;strong&gt;SMoKE&lt;/strong&gt;~[]_ 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://www.skamu.com/icons/animated/images/icon41.gif"
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C6" CUSERID="U147" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Smokey you want a</CSubject>
		<CBody>Smokey you want a demonstration? and free sample Idli ..dosa etc..lol 


&lt;a href="http://photobucket.com/images/funny" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i244.photobucket.com/albums/gg12/N-A-T-A-S-J-A/Funny/smile.gif" border="0" alt="smile Pictures, Images and Photos"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C7" CUSERID="U145" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Smoke..</CSubject>
		<CBody>She used terms like .."we can" or "can be used"

She didn't say she does use..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C8" CUSERID="U148" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Yep brit which is why i said</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yep brit which is why i said she only has knowledge about it and i'm sure never seen or used one  before :p

FS i thought you'd never ask about free samples, my tricks always work..tell me when i should come over :D

Good Fortune always comes knocking at your door...when you are sh*tting in the toilet!! :)
&lt;p&gt;
_[]~&lt;strong&gt;SMoKE&lt;/strong&gt;~[]_ 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;img src="http://www.skamu.com/icons/animated/images/icon41.gif"
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C9" CUSERID="U149" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>wet grinders are available</CSubject>
		<CBody>wet grinders are available at M P Traders. M PT is the main shop selling wet grinders in Doha  . mine I brought from India 5 years back.  </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C10" CUSERID="U57" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>.
.
 :P
.
.
 You can't have</CSubject>
		<CBody>&lt;a href="http://tinypic.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://images.indiaplaza.in/Stores/lg/images/tilting-1.jpg" border="0" alt="/"&gt;
.
.
 &lt;b&gt;:P&lt;/b&gt;
.
.

 &lt;b&gt;You can't have a light without a dark to stick it in!&lt;/b&gt;

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C11" CUSERID="U150" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>thanks drac!! now what, how</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks drac!! now what, how and why is it used?????</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C12" CUSERID="U57" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>.
.
 geez..i am a Drac not</CSubject>
		<CBody>&lt;a href="http://tinypic.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i41.tinypic.com/oi56k2.jpg" border="0" alt="/"&gt;
.
.
 &lt;b&gt;geez..i am a Drac not EINSTEIN! :p&lt;/b&gt;
.
.

 &lt;b&gt;You can't have a light without a dark to stick it in!&lt;/b&gt;

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C13" CUSERID="U151" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I thought you meant a real</CSubject>
		<CBody>I thought you meant a real wet grinder::::

http://www.made-in-china.com/products-search/hot-china-products/Wet_Grinder.html?gclid=CLm0ivzutJoCFQq3sgodsXUpbw

http://www.amazon.com/Grizzly-T10010-10%2522-Wet-Grinder/dp/B00156I10Y

http://pdf.directindustry.com/pdf/scantool-group/wet-grinders/31060-5766.html

http://www.comparestoreprices.co.uk/power-tools/draper-wet-and-dry-bench-grinder-240v.asp

http://www.transtools.co.uk/store/prod_3059/corded-power-tools/bench-grinders/tormek-wet-grinder-supergrind-1206.html


I wouldn't use one of those as a trampoline...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C14" CUSERID="U144" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>birdie</CSubject>
		<CBody>u are absolutely right....i shud have said "indian ladies".....going to change it now..... :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C15" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>what is a wet grinder?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Answers on  the back of a stamp please.


I will hoist that up the flag pole and see who salutes it!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C16" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Cool</CSubject>
		<CBody>I want one then ;-))))


I will hoist that up the flag pole and see who salutes it!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C17" CUSERID="U57" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>.
.
 gosh..."a feckin'</CSubject>
		<CBody>&lt;a href="http://tinypic.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i41.tinypic.com/oi56k2.jpg" border="0" alt="/"&gt;
.
.
 &lt;b&gt;gosh..."a feckin' blender?"
..back in my coffin then...:(&lt;/b&gt;
.
.

 &lt;b&gt;You can't have a light without a dark to stick it in!&lt;/b&gt;

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C18" CUSERID="U144" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>its not a blender you</CSubject>
		<CBody>its not a blender you fool......thats why i said ladies....they wud know the difference!!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C19" CUSERID="U144" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>And stop hijacking my</CSubject>
		<CBody>And stop hijacking my thread.....enough....looking for some useful information here!!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q35_C20" CUSERID="U146" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>FS Thank you ,</CSubject>
		<CBody>for information.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q36" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2009-08-14 18:57:04" QUSERID="U152" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Looking for a therapist in Doha</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi, I was wondering if anyone knows of a decent therapist in Doha. 

I realize that therapy is probably a western concept but with such a large expat community there must be some floating around.

Many thanks for your help.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q36_C1" CUSERID="U153" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I am current studying beauty</CSubject>
		<CBody>I am current studying beauty therapy, if I come to Qatar anytime soon I can help you out lol. What exactly is it you're wanting done?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q36_C2" CUSERID="U11" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Will QL</CSubject>
		<CBody>Online therapist work?
&lt;img src="http://www.qatarliving.com/files/images/Da.gif"&gt;

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q36_C3" CUSERID="U154" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>nice one..</CSubject>
		<CBody>Now we're talkin'...  :D

"Just because it is... IT DOESN'T MEAN IT SHOULD BE.. "

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q36_C4" CUSERID="U155" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>psychotherapy</CSubject>
		<CBody>hi i am shadi i am a psychotherapist ad i am working in doha this is my # 33179773</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q37" QCATEGORY="Advice and Help" QDATE="2012-03-25 18:35:36" QUSERID="U156" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject> Halal Indian food Available in Houston?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Does anybody know where exactly is Halal Indian food available in Houston?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q37_C1" CUSERID="U157" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>did you try</CSubject>
		<CBody>doing some reseacrh on the internet by yourself??

Check this

http://www.bing.com/search?q=halal+indian+food+Houston&amp;src=ie9tr

Regards!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q37_C2" CUSERID="U158" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Hilal Indian food is</CSubject>
		<CBody>Halal Indian food is available at 6202 highway 6 south. moreover 1 halal Chinese &amp; 1 halal Iranian BBQ restaurants are available in hilcroft area.   </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q37_C3" CUSERID="U159" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Wow ! were going global !!</CSubject>
		<CBody>
Wow ! were going global !!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q37_C4" CUSERID="U160" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>LOL Ramil!</CSubject>
		<CBody>I wonder too, what QL had to do with Houston ? o_O ?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q37_C5" CUSERID="U156" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thank you guys</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thank you for your help beepa, galloper and azee. Ramil and khanan internet is known for being global :-)</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q38" QCATEGORY="Electronics" QDATE="2009-08-29 14:05:22" QUSERID="U37" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>PS3 / XBox 360 / Wii Nintendo</QSubject>
	<QBody>I want to buy either a PS3, XBox 360 or Wii. 

Please suggest me which one is good and why?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q38_C1" CUSERID="U161" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: PS3 / XBox 360 / Wii Nintendo</CSubject>
		<CBody>I suggest PS3 .. its a complete entertainment station, not only for gaming but also for:
*watching DIVX movies and Bluray and many other format.
*Store your photos on the system and view them with a nifty album format ..
*Connect to your PC for sharing
*Connect to your PSP if you have one
*Play MP3 and other format songs
and many more ...
An do not forget the variety of awesome games on the shelves now, and some popular ones are under discounted price.

Just my opinion

Regards</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q38_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: PS3 / XBox 360 / Wii Nintendo</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks K_Sama for your valuable piece of advice.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q38_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: PS3 / XBox 360 / Wii Nintendo</CSubject>
		<CBody>No more suggestions?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q38_C4" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: PS3 / XBox 360 / Wii Nintendo</CSubject>
		<CBody>ps3 cuz not alot of ppl buy xbox in qatar...ps3 free network xbox u have to pay monthly or by year</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q38_C5" CUSERID="U162" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: PS3 / XBox 360 / Wii Nintendo</CSubject>
		<CBody>hi
  buy ps3 becoz the most popular games like GOD OF WAR 
TEKKEN KILLZON....etc r only in sony means only in playstation </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q38_C6" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: PS3 / XBox 360 / Wii Nintendo</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks alot guys. I really appreciate ur suggestions. I would definitely go for PS3.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q39" QCATEGORY="Sightseeing and Tourist attractions" QDATE="2012-04-29 11:25:15" QUSERID="U163" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Qmiles for sale</QSubject>
	<QBody>'m aware that Qmiles transfer fee is US$15 per 1,000 Qmiles. (online transfer)

Could you kindly give me an idea how much I can sell my 100,000 Qmiles.

Many thanks.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q39_C1" CUSERID="U164" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Qmiles for sale</CSubject>
		<CBody>The cost of buying 1000 Qmiles directly from Qatar Airways is QR 120. You should accept no less than QR 80 per 1000. Many people would want to spend money on transfer, rather they want you to go with them to the Qatar Airways office to permit the use of the Qmiles you agreed on, they will pay you the agreed amount, and pay Qatar Airways the taxes and other fees.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q39_C2" CUSERID="U164" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Qmiles for sale</CSubject>
		<CBody>"Many people would &lt;b&gt; NOT&lt;/b&gt; want to spend money on transfer"</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q39_C3" CUSERID="U165" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Qmiles for sale</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hi,

Are u still interested in selling Qmiles?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q39_C4" CUSERID="U166" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Qmiles for sale</CSubject>
		<CBody>hi can i purchase your 70,000qmiles..please call me 70013890</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q39_C5" CUSERID="U167" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Qmiles for sale</CSubject>
		<CBody>I want to buy the whole 100000 miles
If OK call me 55018326</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q40" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2009-08-28 13:36:06" QUSERID="U168" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Are there any companies in Qatar that hire out Baby Furniture and Car Seats?</QSubject>
	<QBody>We are moving to Qatar but shipping of all our belongings won't arrive for nearly 5 weeks after we do.  We can't decide if it's best to pay excess bagage and bring items like child port-a-cot and car seat with us or put in shipping.  Is there a company in Qatar that do short term hiring out of items including cots, car seats, high chairs etc?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q40_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Are there any companies in Qatar that hire out Baby...</CSubject>
		<CBody>i saw the same in Lulu / carrefour</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q40_C2" CUSERID="U169" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Are there any companies in Qatar that hire out Baby...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hi
Airlines will not charge you extra for a car seat and travel cot. I have travelled the UK, South Africa and Switzerland and I have always been able to take my stroller, car seat and travel cot with me at no extra charge. Phone the airline and find out!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q40_C3" CUSERID="U170" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Are there any companies in Qatar that hire out Baby...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Definitely phone the airline.  The baggage rules have changed a LOT and we nearly got stung for US$525 for three bags earlier this month. 

As recently as October 2008 you could fly from the U.S. to Doha on Qatar Airways without the carseats counting toward your baggage requirement at all.  In other words, you were allowed two bags per passenger. . .so if there were two adults and two (paying) kids then you were allowed eight bags PLUS the two car seats.  But no longer. . .now you would be allowed six bags plus two car seats.  Anything over that costs US$175 *per bag*.  We learned this the hard way, so it's not an urban legend for us :(

 </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q40_C4" CUSERID="U170" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Are there any companies in Qatar that hire out Baby...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Oh - and to answer your question (sorry 'bout that!) I am not aware of any companies that hire them out.  Car seats, in particular, are generally not used outside of the expatriate crowd. :(

You can find what you need at the City Center Babyshop store, but depending on your luggage situation it might just make sense to bring it with you.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q41" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2009-09-27 21:06:29" QUSERID="U171" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Wanted- Flat For Rent</QSubject>
	<QBody>3 bedroom, 1 hall, 2 bathroom, 1 kitchen............
Expecting for QR 3500- QR 4000.......
Contact no: Mob- 5258839; Lan- 4933193</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q41_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Wanted- Flat For Rent</CSubject>
		<CBody>imposible!</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q42" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2009-09-05 11:01:16" QUSERID="U172" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Where can I get gluten free food from other than Mega Mart in the Center</QSubject>
	<QBody>I am a ceoliac suffer and so need to eat gluten free foor. Does any one know of any other shops in Doha that sell gluten free food other than Mega Mart in the Center ?? Also does any one know of any restaurants selling gluten free food</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q42_C1" CUSERID="U173" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can I get gluten free food from other than Mega...</CSubject>
		<CBody>I suggest you to go to http://www.qatarliving.com/node/617041 where you will get information concerning gluten free food.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q42_C2" CUSERID="U174" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can I get gluten free food from other than Mega...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Mega Mart as everyone says,

I was in the new LULU in Al Gharaffa on Thursday and they had a whole new selection of Gluten Free products. I have also found them sporadilcally in Carrefours.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q42_C3" CUSERID="U174" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can I get gluten free food from other than Mega...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Mega Mart in the centre behind Ramada has the best range that i have found in Doha. I have also found Gluten free products in Carrefour supermarkets and LULU. The new LULU in Al Gharaffa had a whole new range of gluten free products on thursday last week.

Keep in touch via private messsage and i wil assist as best i can.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q42_C4" CUSERID="U175" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can I get gluten free food from other than Mega...</CSubject>
		<CBody> There is Firin Gluten Free Bakery in Qatar newly opened, near Muaither Sports Club, Al Sailiyah Road. Tel: 44661200 Mbl: 33242558. They open from Sat-Thur 4-9 pm Friday closed.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q42_C5" CUSERID="U176" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can I get gluten free food from other than Mega...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Now you can buy full range of gluten-free products from Dr.Schar. (http://www.schar.com/us/gluten-free-products) in Qatar...

You can find these products in Almeera branches like Aldafnah,alwakrah, airport, alnasr and Gean hyper market in Hayyat plaza

..for more details pls call 40165578</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q43" QCATEGORY="Cars" QDATE="2009-05-11 16:36:27" QUSERID="U177" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>urgent</QSubject>
	<QBody> i m buying nissan terrano 2002model,98,000 mileage and asking price is 25,000 can any suggest me abt dis car shd i buy or no,if i will buy wht will b the final price,can any tell me</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q43_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: urgent</CSubject>
		<CBody>i would go for 18,000 provided that car is in good running condition..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q43_C2" CUSERID="U151" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: urgent</CSubject>
		<CBody>abt dis car shd wht will b ???

Please spell correctly, not in shorthand.

I sometimes write this way when I'm taking notes in meetings, but I would fix it when I get to my office.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q43_C3" CUSERID="U136" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: urgent</CSubject>
		<CBody>some people try to be too "fashionable" by writing this type of shorthand.

i know a teenage girl who writes to me emails "hi aunty, dis dat abt" etc etc,,,, That is OK...but I was shocked one day , when her father in 50+, tried to write such language !!!!

it is just another hypocirsy of some Indians, having studied in Indian shcool, suddenly start wrting "I GOTTA GO,, YOU WANNA IT ?"....... such US slangs !!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q43_C4" CUSERID="U178" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: urgent</CSubject>
		<CBody>first do a computer test to see the current condition of vehicle and then decide !!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q43_C5" CUSERID="U179" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: urgent</CSubject>
		<CBody>hi try to buy more cheaper terrano 11 last time i got an offer 16000 QAR only with that same  kilometer and model </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q44" QCATEGORY="Sports in Qatar" QDATE="2012-03-06 02:48:04" QUSERID="U180" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="Yes">
	<QSubject>wanna play squash ?</QSubject>
	<QBody>any1 here would like to go for squash 
2 times per week  
or also if anyone want to learn it and start playing 
feel free to ping me 
cheers</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q44_C1" CUSERID="U181" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>what kind of game is squash?</CSubject>
		<CBody>what kind of game is squash? sorry for ignorance. please enlighten. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q44_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>Squuash</CSubject>
		<CBody>I do not know how to play but i am interested in learning and playing it as it is a good work out  and will be greatfull if i could learn and play this game. 
Regards
Ravi</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q44_C3" CUSERID="U182" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>sounds interesting...
send me</CSubject>
		<CBody>sounds interesting...

send me your pin to ping you </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q44_C4" CUSERID="U183" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>Don't know how to play</CSubject>
		<CBody>Don't know how to play squash, but love to learn.. I'm in as well.. 
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q45" QCATEGORY="Electronics" QDATE="2009-08-16 21:35:08" QUSERID="U184" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Wii or PS2</QSubject>
	<QBody>hi everyone, I want to buy a game console for my 6year old daughter. So far have checked some options but needed some advice on which one is better of the two? thanks.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q45_C1" CUSERID="U185" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Wii or PS2</CSubject>
		<CBody>I PRFER U TO BUY A WII 4 UR 6 YEAR OLD CHILD BECAUSE PS2 IS JUS SITING AND PALYING KIND OG GAME BUT WII IS...KINDA EXERSISE GAME LIKE MOVING....SO BUY A WII</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q45_C2" CUSERID="U186" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Wii or PS2</CSubject>
		<CBody>I would suggest WII aswell because u can both sit down in one place &amp; play games or get up &amp; start moving while playing. Its the best for kids that age.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q45_C3" CUSERID="U187" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Wii or PS2</CSubject>
		<CBody>WII, itsmore fun for childern of her age,,,and most of its games are for kids!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q45_C4" CUSERID="U188" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Wii or PS2</CSubject>
		<CBody>WII is better in these both exercise too </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q45_C5" CUSERID="U184" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Wii or PS2</CSubject>
		<CBody>thankyou all</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q46" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2008-12-24 07:54:22" QUSERID="U145" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Where's the best Manicure ?</QSubject>
	<QBody>My buddy Pajju is in need of a manicure. (see attached) 

Where's the best place ?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q46_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>ewwwwwwwwww</CSubject>
		<CBody>I shouldnt have seen that, I was eating an apple and now I feel sick, that guy is really letterly 'twisted'..lol</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q46_C2" CUSERID="U189" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Darude: he goes to the</CSubject>
		<CBody>Darude: he goes to the bathroom with those hands too</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q46_C3" CUSERID="U190" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>brite </CSubject>
		<CBody>lolzzzzzz :) but he s not wearin LUNGI :) anyway wow wow amazing :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q47" QCATEGORY="Sports in Qatar" QDATE="2013-08-20 16:23:49" QUSERID="U191" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Just Gym</QSubject>
	<QBody>So I had a wander down to this gym today.

The guys at the front desk were happy for me to walk around and take a look and were not pushy at all.

All I can say is that the facility is amazing and if you have the money and are serious to get in shape then definitely check it out! :-)</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q47_C1" CUSERID="U192" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Qatar Fitness Center season ticket for sale </CSubject>
		<CBody>am selling season ticket (attendance hours from 8am to 12 midnight , Friday is off)Qatar Fitness Center is located in Al - Muntazah area, valid till 17.02.2014.The price is negotiable , transferring fee is 100qar. Call me at +97477596124.Dennis
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q48" QCATEGORY="Sightseeing and Tourist attractions" QDATE="2009-03-29 21:25:26" QUSERID="U193" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Going to Bahrain?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi,
Me and 2 of my friends want to go to Bahrain for a weekend for a visit. We are all 16, 2 of us are from UK and 1 is from India.
Will we be allowed to buy tickets and fly there? Also, will we be able to get visas in Bahrain? And how much will they cost?

Thanks</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q48_C1" CUSERID="U194" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Going to Bahrain?</CSubject>
		<CBody>you can get visa on arrival. juz get the ticket and fly bahrain. Enjoy weekend,,,safely</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q48_C2" CUSERID="U195" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Going to Bahrain?</CSubject>
		<CBody>I guess the Indean fellow would need a visa from the Bahraini Embassy in Doha, i dont think he is eligible for visa on arrival..

all the best</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q48_C3" CUSERID="U196" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Going to Bahrain?</CSubject>
		<CBody>You can now check your eligibility for a Bahrain visa online by visiting the link http://www.evisa.gov.bh
3, 7 and 14 days visas are issued online for all Nationalities.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q48_C4" CUSERID="U193" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Going to Bahrain?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks very much!!

That website is especially useful.

I'm glad I can make this trip happen now :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q48_C5" CUSERID="U197" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Going to Bahrain?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Since you guys from UK, you can get visa on arrival but bad news for that indian. He can not get visa that way. So exclude indian.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q48_C6" CUSERID="U198" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Going to Bahrain?</CSubject>
		<CBody>zoso! , what u mean exclude the indian? I AM THE INDIAN
fawk that i am going ! if they dont let me fly there, i will swim !</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q49" QCATEGORY="Family Life in Qatar" QDATE="2012-03-24 15:01:10" QUSERID="U199" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>another question about sponsorship</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hypothetically speaking: If a wife that arrived on husband's sponsorship gets a job, and wants to leave that job for another better paying job, can she do it without any restricions?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q49_C1" CUSERID="U200" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>if the wife is under the</CSubject>
		<CBody>if the wife is under the sponsorship of his husband he can freely tranfer to any company.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q49_C2" CUSERID="U201" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>she</CSubject>
		<CBody>can she works with gov under her husband sponsring as well ?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q49_C3" CUSERID="U202" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>the only restriction is COURTESY,</CSubject>
		<CBody>better to follow the terms in the Labor Law regarding terminating a contract by either party.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q49_C4" CUSERID="U19" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Well, it's a bit more complex</CSubject>
		<CBody>Well, it's a bit more complex than that. If she gets a job that allows her to stay under her husband's sponsorship she can change without an NOC. Some jobs require you be under their sponsorship.
Mandi</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q50" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2010-09-06 16:17:38" QUSERID="U203" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Souq Waqif Timings</QSubject>
	<QBody>What are the Souq timings for this week and Eid? Thank you.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q50_C1" CUSERID="U203" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Anyone?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Anyone?</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q51" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2011-05-29 11:11:39" QUSERID="U37" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Transfer of sponsorship</QSubject>
	<QBody>One of my colleagues has already used his tranfer of sponsorship facility three times, now due to recession and loss of work he wants to use this facility for a fourth time. Is it possible and permitted for transfer of sponsorship to be done for a fourth time or is it only limited to three times(maximum). </QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q51_C1" CUSERID="U204" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>thanks for the info sambs</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks... a lot.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q51_C2" CUSERID="U205" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>it seems difficult 4rth time</CSubject>
		<CBody> it seems difficult 4rth time the transfer of sponsorship, thrice is ordinary. but if u have some reliable source(wasta) in immigration, would be ok then.

even if current company let you free to work anywhere, but immigration might be an obstacle.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q51_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>It's fine dear.... as long as</CSubject>
		<CBody>It's fine dear.... as long as you pay for it, it's ok....you can change sponsorships as mush as you want as long as you have NOC. I myself changed 5 times. So no worries...</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q52" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2008-10-27 07:23:34" QUSERID="U206" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Greek Embassy</QSubject>
	<QBody>Wheres the Greek Embassy in Doha?  Contact details would be appreciated...

Thanks! :)</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q52_C1" CUSERID="U207" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Greek Embassy</CSubject>
		<CBody>Consular services for Greek nationals

Cyprus Embassy in Doha is represents the consular interests and diplomatic protection of Greek nationals who live and work in Qatar since there is no Greek Embassy in the country.

Greek nationals can certify documents, signatures and ask for a permanent resident certificate. The price for the certifications is 5 (around QR40 depending on exchange rate)

Also Cyprus Embassy keeps a mailing list where Greeks and Cypriots who live and work in Qatar are encouraged to register. The mailing list is updated daily and every effort is made for the best accuracy. The Embassy distributes security information when necessary and other important information to the registered nationals.

The Greek Ambassador to Qatar is the Ambassador of Greek Embassy in Kuwait. Since Cyprus has not started issuing shengen visas yet, visa applications for Greece are being processed by the Embassy of France.

For more information please contact the consular section of the Embassy.

check this link, http://www.mfa.gov.cy/mfa/Embassies/Embassy_Doha.nsf/All/85D1B7B79AB8FFFE432571D4002E8729?OpenDocument
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q52_C2" CUSERID="U208" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Greek Embassy</CSubject>
		<CBody>try this one:
P.O box 15721 Doha-Qatar
tel(00974)4128150</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q52_C3" CUSERID="U209" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Greek Embassy</CSubject>
		<CBody>It is near Inter Continental hotel.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q52_C4" CUSERID="U210" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Greek Embassy</CSubject>
		<CBody>It had recently opened and the prime minister of the Greece was here for the last 3 days,

it is near Intercontinental Hotel Roundabout, go to the left from the RB and then first right, you will find a sign for Greek Embassy, Bahrain Embassy and Chouefat School (Sabis)

the information below about the Cyprus embassy is old and obselete

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q52_C5" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Greek Embassy</CSubject>
		<CBody>The first answer is outdated - it should be deleted. 

There is a Greek embassy in Qatar and its hours are 10-12 daily except Fridays. 

Location 
 
Opposite the Doha exibition center. 

If you are driving from City Center and make a U-turn at the Doha Exibition Center Round about. In about 400 meters make a right turn. Once you made the right, follow through - maybe the second right and another right till you see some vans belonging to a construction office. You will find the Greek Embassy close to them.

412 8150 Greek Embassy Phone Number  </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q53" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2008-12-17 15:45:44" QUSERID="U211" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>employment band</QSubject>
	<QBody>help!!who is imposing a 2 yrs band?company or immigration?like in my case i resigned from work,my visa is expired but the company gave me a release,if i will go back to my country will i have an employment band???and needs to wait for 2 yrs to finish to enter doha again?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q53_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: employment band</CSubject>
		<CBody>From what I know, you will be ban from Qatar if your employment did not give a release and you will have to wait for at least two years to go back to Qatar.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q53_C2" CUSERID="U212" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: employment band</CSubject>
		<CBody>if you get the no objection certificate from current sponsor u can enter in doha with valid visa</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q53_C3" CUSERID="U109" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: employment band</CSubject>
		<CBody>your sponsor can ban you for lifetime,5 years and minimum 2 years .this 2 year ban is by govt.it is common for anybody who cancel rp and went out.more than 2 yrs ban your sponsor have to show solid reason to mini of interior and it is very hard for employers.
now if you want to return before 2 years,noc is requried from old sponsor.if you carry noc with you at time of dept,it need to be endorsed by immigration and this endorsement will expire automaticaly after 6 months.in that case your new employer have to get another one to get your new visa.
but wait,,,,,,,which visa are you?some type of visa does not need 2 years bar.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q53_C4" CUSERID="U213" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: employment band</CSubject>
		<CBody>If u hv NOC U can come, make sure you Get ur RP cancelled by your current company before leaving, make sure you have not crossed 3 months of Expiry of RP.
Why don't you get sponsorship changed since U have release. GOOD LUCK!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q53_C5" CUSERID="U211" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: employment band</CSubject>
		<CBody>actually my papers are in the labor dept. we are applying for my change of sponsorship we were rejected twice,the reason is the immigration imposed a new rule that company sponsorship transferred to husband sponsorship are not allowed or vice versa..now my visa is expired and i need to go back home that's why i am asking if i will go back home will i be able to come back here in qatar after my 2 months vacation,by the way i have my NOC w/ me and release paper from my previous company.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q54" QCATEGORY="Socialising" QDATE="2012-08-07 14:55:22" QUSERID="U214" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>A social Circle</QSubject>
	<QBody>I wish i can create a pool of friends here,having get together in the weekend and getting partners to hit the dance floors.
Just flashing back good old memories of College days where friends circle were awesome. meeting new gals n boys are so easy and lyf full on the rocksss

Can we do it here....???</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q54_C1" CUSERID="U214" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>i love it..:))</CSubject>
		<CBody>i love it..:))</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q55" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2012-07-11 16:22:17" QUSERID="U215" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>penalty for unclaimed new plate number</QSubject>
	<QBody>will there be a fine/penalty for not claiming the new plate number after three months? if there is any, how much? please i need response from those who have experienced the same. thank you.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q55_C1" CUSERID="U216" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: penalty for unclaimed new plate number</CSubject>
		<CBody>how can you "claim " one?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q55_C2" CUSERID="U217" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: penalty for unclaimed new plate number</CSubject>
		<CBody>i am not sure if there is any penalty but they tell you if you dont collect within 30 Days the number plate is scrapped and you will have to pay for the plates again, i think its 250 QAR for two.

But try to go back to the traffic department just incase your plate is still there you can say you went out on holidays or so .. just give it a shot...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q55_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: penalty for unclaimed new plate number</CSubject>
		<CBody>There is no penalty but you have to apply again for a new plate.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q55_C4" CUSERID="U215" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>thanks for your comments. yes</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks for your comments. yes, there was no penalty but we paid for the new plate. </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q56" QCATEGORY="Life in Qatar" QDATE="2011-04-22 22:16:16" QUSERID="U218" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="Unsure">
	<QSubject>is it truth that they will sent you to jail if the police caught you dating with someone?</QSubject>
	<QBody>i mean if they caught you dating someone who is not your husband or wife?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q56_C1" CUSERID="U219" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Unsure">
		<CSubject>RE: is it truth that they will sent you to jail if the...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Dating isn't an issue, its having a sexual relationship that is the issue.
I think jail would come into it if one of the parties was married.
Still, could be worse, its stoning in some other countries!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q56_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Unsure">
		<CSubject>RE: is it truth that they will sent you to jail if the...</CSubject>
		<CBody>well yes, if they find you kissing or _____ in public or even in room (if some one saw you and complain)
so better be careful. dating is not a issue, doing something nasty will bring trouble for you.
so Ms strawberry, u can go for date ...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q56_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is it truth that they will sent you to jail if the...</CSubject>
		<CBody>haha....guess ur in shit ...why did u do this ?</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q57" QCATEGORY="Advice and Help" QDATE="2010-03-18 11:35:11" QUSERID="U220" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Calculators</QSubject>
	<QBody>Some good work done using Excel.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q57_C1" CUSERID="U147" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thx for sharing...the</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thx for sharing...the qualities mentioned there is exactly me !! :)


&lt;a href="http://photobucket.com/images/love%20peace%20happiness" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i633.photobucket.com/albums/uu51/mariaalejandra_2009/peace_love_happiness.jpg" border="0" alt="PEACE Pictures, Images and Photos"/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q58" QCATEGORY="Environment" QDATE="2009-09-05 22:47:00" QUSERID="U221" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>removed by mod</QSubject>
	<QBody>post in classifieds</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q58_C1" CUSERID="U57" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Prado!
.</CSubject>
		<CBody>&lt;a href="http://tinypic.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i41.tinypic.com/oi56k2.jpg" border="0" alt="/"&gt;

 &lt;b&gt;Prado!&lt;/b&gt;
.

&lt;a href="http://tinypic.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i27.tinypic.com/3469ks7.jpg" border="0" alt="</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q59" QCATEGORY="Electronics" QDATE="2012-07-19 00:57:15" QUSERID="U222" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>mac book pro</QSubject>
	<QBody>i want to switch to mac. where is the best place to buy mac book pro.. apple store at mall is little expensive.. can any one suggest bit cheaper store around doha..


</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q59_C1" CUSERID="U222" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: mac book pro</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks guys.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q60" QCATEGORY="Advice and Help" QDATE="2009-05-11 16:30:46" QUSERID="U223" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>What to call my cat?</QSubject>
	<QBody>I recently came home with a Puddy Tat from Qaws and cant think of a name. Its a male. Can someone tell me what "cat"is in arabic please?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q60_C1" CUSERID="U224" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>lilbo </CSubject>
		<CBody>have you got a name already?

&lt;a href="http://www.yescomments.com" title="MySpace Comments"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i107.photobucket.com/albums/m282/pure100/com2/smile/smile007.gif" border="0" alt="myspace comments"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q60_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Rover??</CSubject>
		<CBody>Be different.


I will hoist that up the flag pole and see who salutes it!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q61" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2012-01-08 11:06:29" QUSERID="U37" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Bringing Books From Sharjah To Qatar</QSubject>
	<QBody>Dear Qlers, 

can you please advise how i can bring some books from dubai to Qatar

books belong to physiotherapy used books for my reference.
appreciate your kind guidance. 

5-6 books only </QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q61_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Bringing Books From Sharjah To Qatar</CSubject>
		<CBody>many thanks for your valued support but as usual books are heavy around 8-9 kgs total. if i use postal am sure i will end up paying a huge charges
any other alternative..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q61_C2" CUSERID="U225" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Bringing Books From Sharjah To Qatar</CSubject>
		<CBody>well, then i guess you could check and see who is coming to qatar from dubai, and request them to get the books for you. but to be honest, i don't think anyone would be willing to fill in 8-9 kgs of their own luggage space, just to get books for someone else! , thinkin this way, you might find the shipment option more helpful! 
you might have to do a little homework on checking out which shipment companies gives you the best price, and instruct the seller/sender accordingly :)

alternately, try looking for those books in qatar, i.e. in jarir bookstore. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q61_C3" CUSERID="U59" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Bringing Books From Sharjah To Qatar</CSubject>
		<CBody>ani chy has given you the right answer. If you dont want to spend money on shipping charges you should find someone who is coming from U.A.E and also willing to take you 9kg load free of charge but most probably a very difficult way.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q61_C4" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Bringing Books From Sharjah To Qatar</CSubject>
		<CBody>CONTACT:
 
E2E GLOBAL LINES
RENJITH KR
OPERATIONS SUPERVISOR
MOB:77157771
EMAIL:renjith@e2eqatar.com</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q61_C5" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Bringing Books From Sharjah To Qatar</CSubject>
		<CBody>You can check http://www.qatarusedbooks.wordpress.com. They advertise your used books on the website, or you can simply donate it. They just opened a facebook page http://www.facebook.com/UsedBookStoreQatar in which there going to be a community of people interested in book swapping, opening a book club etc.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q62" QCATEGORY="Life in Qatar" QDATE="2010-07-08 11:15:09" QUSERID="U226" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>About Resignation?</QSubject>
	<QBody>One of my friend is working here in Qatar for 4 years,he is planning to resign and go back to his country of origin.He was asking does the company will give any seperation pay?if yes,how is it to be computed?lenght of service or whatsoever?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q62_C1" CUSERID="U227" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: About Resignation?</CSubject>
		<CBody>gratuity -40 days of basic salary he will get ,since he worked 4 years .</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q62_C2" CUSERID="U228" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: About Resignation?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Per Qatar labor laws: 21 days basic salary is gratuity for each year worked.

4 year * 21 days * last daily basic pay = Gratuity Amount</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q62_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: About Resignation?</CSubject>
		<CBody>1-calculation of gratuity as per qatar labor law is 21 days basic salary of each year. if u worked 5 years or more it will become 1 month basic salary instead of 21 days. 
2. Each year u have a right to get 21 days leave salry, if u not get in previous years, u can claim for this also.
3. All of the calculation based on the last basic salary u got. Eg. suppose on the time of ur joining ur basic salary is 5000 and now u r getting the basic salary 7500, the calculation is based on the last one measns 7500.
4. If ur contract is defenit contract u should give 2 weeks notice informing ur resignation. if ur contact is indefinit duration contact u must give 1 month notice about ur resignation. other wise they can deduct 1 month salary or remaining balance of days salary from ur settlement.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q62_C4" CUSERID="U44" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: About Resignation?</CSubject>
		<CBody>he will get only gratuity that 21 days per year as per the last drawn basic, apart from that legally nothing</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q63" QCATEGORY="Salary and Allowances" QDATE="2009-11-16 18:45:10" QUSERID="U229" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>is 2750 QR gonna be enough?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hello internet. I'm about to work in Qatar. Is 2750 gonna be enough? What do you think? Free accommodation and transportation to the office!</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q63_C1" CUSERID="U230" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is 2750 QR gonna be enough?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hello Queenritz!

Although the accommodation and transportation is provided, the offer is really lame and you'll see that won't be enough for your monthly expenses.
Good luck!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q63_C2" CUSERID="U231" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is 2750 QR gonna be enough?</CSubject>
		<CBody>if you spend it moderately then, 750qr is enough for the whole month food and other expense.

you can save upto 2000qr, if you spend the money correctly.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q63_C3" CUSERID="U232" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is 2750 QR gonna be enough?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Very Bad Offer, keep trying better luck next time.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q63_C4" CUSERID="U233" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is 2750 QR gonna be enough?</CSubject>
		<CBody>can u tell which school u will join  u can earn some money by tution also if it is bright future pakisatani school then it is good</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q63_C5" CUSERID="U234" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is 2750 QR gonna be enough?</CSubject>
		<CBody>This to Nasim.... lol
u made me laugh truely..he said QR.2750
Means clear enogh he will spend qatari reyals..wat QR.750 for his food and and wat other expenses(intrnet,tel,laundry,etc..)and save QR.2000
be realist man no matter how u moderat and tighten ur self unless u meant to spend QR.2000 and SAVE QR.750 !!???..
lol...are u replying from india or where else on the moon.


my dear it's too low rate..try to negotiate harder it doesnt worth..unless u desperatly u need ajob </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q63_C6" CUSERID="U235" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is 2750 QR gonna be enough?</CSubject>
		<CBody>you are young and i guess its your first time to work abroad. go for it, don't expect much. when u grow and get the experience, then you can bargain for best offer. GOODLUCK!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q63_C7" CUSERID="U236" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is 2750 QR gonna be enough?</CSubject>
		<CBody>2750 is too much for you. tell the management to reduce salary  range 1500 to 1750, then they will definitely agree with you and you should think that teaching profession is not for money, its a charity too...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q63_C8" CUSERID="U237" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: is 2750 QR gonna be enough?</CSubject>
		<CBody>It would be enough but not satisfactory. Just do your job very well and soon you can ask for an increase.

Regards</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q64" QCATEGORY="Family Life in Qatar" QDATE="2009-05-18 12:20:46" QUSERID="U238" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>where can i find a good house maid can any one suggest please</QSubject>
	<QBody>I am looking for a housemaid. i am a muslim with 4 family members.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q64_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: where can i find a good house maid can any one...</CSubject>
		<CBody>all good housemaids will be employed by good families...now all available are good for nothing.!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q64_C2" CUSERID="U239" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: where can i find a good house maid can any one...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hmmm.... your probably better off going to that pet shop and purchasing one of those Baboons.   Good luck, if you find the answer please, post it.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q64_C3" CUSERID="U240" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: where can i find a good house maid can any one...</CSubject>
		<CBody>You only know by try and error
start with 3 months hire and see
if good take it if not changed
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q65" QCATEGORY="Salary and Allowances" QDATE="2012-08-09 21:09:58" QUSERID="U241" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Is 14500 qar good salary</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi All,

I got a job offer from qatar they are offering me 14500 per month  and 4000 bonus that would be paid quarterly. This is way more than what I get in India .But do you think this is a good salary in Qatar . I am married and my wife would join me.How much would I be able to save on average a month.

Thank you in advance.
</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q65_C1" CUSERID="U242" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Is 14500 qar good salary</CSubject>
		<CBody>14,500 is a good salary and the bonus is a plus, u will be paying the rent per month for a 2 Bedroom fully furnished apartment between 7000 to 8000 QR, around 300 for water and electricity bills, then monthly budget for groceries approx. 1000 to 1500. so all in all maximum 10,000 QR, so will be saving around 5,000QR at least.u can save more depending on the life style u choose. life in qatar is good, peaceful, free of worries. so don't worry take a chance , its a good opportunity.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q65_C2" CUSERID="U243" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Is 14500 qar good salary</CSubject>
		<CBody>You can find 1BHK semi furnished brand new flats including water and electricity in Doha at Qrs 3500-4000 per month. Grocery, 1000- 1500 Qrs. Petrol and other maintenances, 300-500 if you have an economy car in good condition. Telephone and internet, 250-500. So total monthly expense will come around 6500 - 7000 maximum. You can save half of your salary if you have a good plan. Good luck go ahead this is a good job offer if the company and project is real.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q65_C3" CUSERID="U244" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Is 14500 qar good salary</CSubject>
		<CBody>For single it is okay. But for married you won't be saving anything. 1000-1500 living expenses is good for one person only. House rent and food will eat most of your salary. Transportation or car maintenance and education fees is an additional burden to your meagre salary.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q65_C4" CUSERID="U241" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Is 14500 qar good salary</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks for your inputs.Felt this is a good salary by Asian Standards.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q65_C5" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Is 14500 qar good salary</CSubject>
		<CBody>i dont see anybody died here with a salary of 1000QR...depends on your lifestyle...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q65_C6" CUSERID="U245" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Is 14500 qar good salary</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yes it's more than good and you don't have a family so easily you can pay your home rent and your car Car payments , the rest of your salary you can do some shopping and spend a good time with friends</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q66" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2012-03-08 10:47:13" QUSERID="U246" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="No">
	<QSubject>Car Transfer</QSubject>
	<QBody>One of my friend is on visit visa in Qatar, he got permanent Qatari Driving license, can he buy car on his name though he dont have Residence visa?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q66_C1" CUSERID="U59" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Car Transfer</CSubject>
		<CBody>How did he get a Qatari Driving License (permanent) without having a Residence Permit and ID?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q66_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>RE: Car Transfer</CSubject>
		<CBody>cherukkan, He might have got the temporary DL and is confused. They will not issue Permanent DL without RP and ID. 

A person on visit visa will not have a Permanent DL of Qatar and will not be able to buy a car.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q66_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>RE: Car Transfer</CSubject>
		<CBody>please get your facts straight as you cannot get a Permanent Drivers License without an RP. The license is link to your QID and bear the same number.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q66_C4" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Unsure">
		<CSubject>RE: Car Transfer</CSubject>
		<CBody>the license is connected to the Qatari ID.. if the visa is cancelled the license will have no meaning as well.. he is driving at his own risk similar to not having a license.. if he gets a new sponsor and gets a new qatari id he will again need to apply for a new license to be linked to that new ID.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q66_C5" CUSERID="U59" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>RE: Car Transfer</CSubject>
		<CBody>Dohamarketing is right. You don't need a Driving License to buy a car but you need an RP to buy a car. His Driving License is invalid as his visa was cancelled and he should renew it after obtaining the RP.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q67" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2010-03-08 06:40:41" QUSERID="U247" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>visa for wife,w/out nso authen. marriage cert</QSubject>
	<QBody>To all my fellow Filipinos please advice. . I just asked my wife, she said it will take time for us to get a NSO authenticated marriage certificate, we only have the original marriage certificate from our Local civil registrar. . . can we used this to get a visit visa for her? What are our options? </QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q67_C1" CUSERID="U248" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Repost!
http://www.qatarlivi.</CSubject>
		<CBody>Repost!

http://www.qatarliving.com/node/945020

It's not because things are difficult that we don't dare, it's because we don't dare that makes things difficult!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q67_C2" CUSERID="U247" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>wife's family visit visa</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks for your reply. . i will ask my wife to check again. .i have one more question, she is still using her maiden name in her passport, does she need to change it or we can use it as it is?

thanks you very much for your help. . .</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q67_C3" CUSERID="U247" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>visa for my wife</CSubject>
		<CBody>chevydjak, thank you very much for your reply. . actually my wife already went to NSO serbilis center in our city just today and will get the authenticated certificate soon . . we got married in the phils just last month during my vacation. . so after getting authentication she just need to go to DFA for red ribon, is it correct? . . . and regarding her passport , does she need to change her surname to my surname or we can use it as it is? . . thanks in advance. .

God bless</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q67_C4" CUSERID="U24" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>if you have time ....</CSubject>
		<CBody>it is better to change her passport, but if not I think it's fine.

My housemate is the same situation with u the only difference is; they get married here, in Qatar...

yeah you're right after NSO...DFA authentication... then she need to send it here in Qatar for our Embassy's Authentication....

BTW...u want me to post this in Filex Group? So that, our fellow Filipinos could help u :)

&lt;b&gt;"BRING IT ON CHAKA DOLL!!!"&lt;/b&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q67_C5" CUSERID="U24" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Hello Olie...</CSubject>
		<CBody>I have posted it in Filexpat group...pls follow this link.

http://www.qatarliving.com/node/945207

&lt;b&gt;"BRING IT ON CHAKA DOLL!!!"&lt;/b&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q67_C6" CUSERID="U247" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>thanks</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks again . . . yah please kindly post it. . my subcription request to filex group was rejected. . i dont have enough points. . thanks again. . </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q68" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2009-07-09 09:35:53" QUSERID="U249" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>19,000 QR QDC ration??? WTF??? </QSubject>
	<QBody>Checked my limit yesterday...
I could open a pub for that amount???
</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q68_C1" CUSERID="U250" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>FS</CSubject>
		<CBody>  
 ;)  
______________________________________________

- Listen to Many...Speak to a Few -</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q69" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2011-04-29 14:26:47" QUSERID="U37" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Kate-William wedding fotos.</QSubject>
	<QBody>God bless them both...Amen.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q69_C1" CUSERID="U251" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>oh dear!</CSubject>
		<CBody>oh dear!</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q70" QCATEGORY="Beauty and Style" QDATE="2008-12-12 19:30:10" QUSERID="U252" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>perfumes</QSubject>
	<QBody>What is the best perfumes for men and women?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C1" CUSERID="U253" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>chanel...the best ever...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>The one that is best for me is not necessarily the best for you so this question will not give you the right answer.  for me Porsche Design is the best</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C3" CUSERID="U254" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>Kenzo, Dior , Gucci, Paco Rabanne, versace</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C4" CUSERID="U255" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>Euphoria for women by calvin klien &amp; Lacoste essential for Men sooooooooo sexy... LOVE IT!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C5" CUSERID="U256" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>try HUGO Energized</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C6" CUSERID="U257" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>Him : 1 Million by Paco Rabanne, Gucci pour homme 2
Her : Nina Richi Gold edition, Into the blue by Escada </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C7" CUSERID="U258" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>Perfume is a personal matter. It depends on your personality, your look, your mood and especially on your environement (they are the ones who gonna smell it). The perfume you wear at a party may be very inappropriate at work. You should  be careful as well beacause some people may have "allergies".
Go with you feeling.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C8" CUSERID="U259" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>what he loves on me: Givenchy Very Irresistable and Bulgari Omnia. what i love on him: RL Polo Black and Givenchy Neo.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C9" CUSERID="U260" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>If you are trying to give someone a gift,
ask one of her friend.

Perfumes comes in different smell to different people and there are perfumes that are nice for hot weather and some in cold.



</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C10" CUSERID="U261" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hmm...if you want to have a perfume in z low cost then i would say DOUBLE HORSe or France CLUB

N if u want to in moderate ones the ni say VERSACE , PORCHE design , 1001 nights ( atar ) , HUGO or BOSS</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C11" CUSERID="U262" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>It differs in taste from person to person..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q70_C12" CUSERID="U263" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: perfumes</CSubject>
		<CBody>For Men: Curve Crush (Liz Claiborne)
For Women: Calvin Klein or Blue Lady</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q71" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2009-05-01 13:46:21" QUSERID="U146" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Handbags - serious question for the ladies</QSubject>
	<QBody>Just been arguing with the hubby.. would like your opinion on the matter..

When chosing handbags, do you go for a brand name or looks and practicality ?

Do brand names actually offer value ?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q71_C1" CUSERID="U224" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>i go for the looks and practicality</CSubject>
		<CBody>
&lt;a href="http://www.yescomments.com" title="MySpace Comments"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i107.photobucket.com/albums/m282/pure100/com2/smile/smile007.gif" border="0" alt="myspace comments"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q72" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2011-06-20 10:01:45" QUSERID="U264" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Passport Renewal</QSubject>
	<QBody>Can anybody give me any idea of how long will it take to renew a passport in the Philippine Embassy and how much will it cost me?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q72_C1" CUSERID="U202" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>the rule says,</CSubject>
		<CBody>&lt;p&gt;you need to have a valid passport of six months when you travel!&amp;nbsp; It's safe you extend it now and when you come back, have it renewed here.&amp;nbsp; There might be complications!&lt;/p&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q72_C2" CUSERID="U265" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Passport renewal</CSubject>
		<CBody>&lt;p&gt;I can extend it here in our embassy? any idea how much its cost? thanks for the reply&lt;/p&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q72_C3" CUSERID="U266" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>passport extension will cost</CSubject>
		<CBody>passport extension will cost you 200 riyals..good for 3 months...i think.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q72_C4" CUSERID="U202" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>go to the links</CSubject>
		<CBody>in the Filex group, you'll know all the details! Even if you are not a member of Filex, you can browse it!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q72_C5" CUSERID="U267" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>30 to 45 days</CSubject>
		<CBody>30 to 45 days</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q72_C6" CUSERID="U268" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Try calling the Embassy and</CSubject>
		<CBody>Try calling the Embassy and ask for details.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q72_C7" CUSERID="U269" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I heard it takes about 1</CSubject>
		<CBody>I heard it takes about 1 month for the PP Renewal...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q72_C8" CUSERID="U202" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>why do you wish</CSubject>
		<CBody>for a month?  Actually, before they say maximum 45 days, but lately (like what happened to my wife and her friends, almost two months!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q72_C9" CUSERID="U266" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>angel - it's two months for</CSubject>
		<CBody>angel - it's two months for passport renewal.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q72_C10" CUSERID="U264" CGOLD="Not English" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>mga kabayan, tanong ko</CSubject>
		<CBody>mga kabayan, tanong ko lang..kung magpaparenew ba ng passport dito eh magpapaschedule sa philippine embassy tulad sa pilipinas?

ano ang requirements na need ko iprepare for passport renewal?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q72_C11" CUSERID="U202" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>angel, you are in the main forum,</CSubject>
		<CBody>so you need to post in english, although almost all who replied are "kabayans" (it's a rule in QL).

Check the link as given by TD!

Since you will get an e-Passport, just the old passport, original and photocopied (you'll keep the original after the verification), and the payment.  Of course you need to fill-up the renewal form!
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q73" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2012-12-05 10:30:27" QUSERID="U270" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>What will be the best gift for women this christmas ?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Christmas is around a corner. Then If we think about the gifts then If we want to  "Gift For Her"(mother, sister, girls, girlfriends, wife) then what will be the best options like jewelries, dress, gift cards, ring, diamonds, make up kit etc.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q73_C1" CUSERID="U271" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What will be the best gift for women this christmas ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>give cash... they will much like that way. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q73_C2" CUSERID="U272" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What will be the best gift for women this christmas ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>gold always works and chocolate ;)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q73_C3" CUSERID="U273" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What will be the best gift for women this christmas ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>IPhone 5...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q73_C4" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What will be the best gift for women this christmas ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>It would be better to be specific that whom you are gonna present a gift. because women at different ages have different tastes </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q73_C5" CUSERID="U270" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What will be the best gift for women this christmas ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>I think chocolates and money are very common gift but . If we think about the jewelry and pendant , necklace or ring etc ,May be best gift for women . I think jewelries are most beautiful things that women will definitely love . 
&lt;img src="http://images.doba.com/products/3863/mod_images_image_czsetliezel.jpg" height="250" width="250"&gt;

 I found it at &lt;a href="http://ergode.com/christmas/gift-for-her" rel="dofollow"&gt;Christmas gift for her&lt;/a&gt; section of ergode. 
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q73_C6" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What will be the best gift for women this christmas ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>There are too many gift offers by some awesome skincare brands like http://www.dermology.us/  and  http://www.defensesoap.com/ in this Christmas. I got one and presented it to my mother. This can be an option as women are most likely to appreciate it. </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q74" QCATEGORY="Education" QDATE="2009-12-01 15:25:48" QUSERID="U274" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Does anybody know where is MES(stationary shop)?</QSubject>
	<QBody>MES was located opposite to GARDEN RESTAURANT before relocation now the building has been demolished.am trying to know its new location.kindly tell me if someone knows about it!  </QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q74_C1" CUSERID="U275" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Does anybody know where is MES(stationary shop)?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Here is the Google map pointer to the new location.

http://maps.google.com/maps/ms?ie=UTF8&amp;hl=en&amp;msa=0&amp;ll=25.247702,51.566699&amp;spn=0.003799,0.004989&amp;t=h&amp;z=18&amp;msid=114441572627272989343.000479ab34b4cae9a8c90

Basically, going from Airport Signal to E-Ring, it is in the building just before UPS (parcel company).</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q74_C2" CUSERID="U232" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Does anybody know where is MES(stationary shop)?</CSubject>
		<CBody>It is behind MES school, near Baby CARE, they are planning to shift to new showroom in Old Airport Road shortly.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q74_C3" CUSERID="U31" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Does anybody know where is MES(stationary shop)?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Dear they will be shortly moving to their new premises which is located at Airport road near to United Parcel Services ( UPS ). 

Regards</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q75" QCATEGORY="Sightseeing and Tourist attractions" QDATE="2010-10-05 19:51:01" QUSERID="U276" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>how can i travel from qatar to australia</QSubject>
	<QBody>help from every one.how con i travel from qatar to australia?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C1" CUSERID="U277" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>Get in touch with a travel agency and they can work out the itinerary for you.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C2" CUSERID="U278" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>By plane.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C3" CUSERID="U48" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>Get yourself the visa and book yourself a ticket to fly to Australia.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C4" CUSERID="U279" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>Qatar Airways fly direct from Doha to Melbourne.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C5" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>Get ur "exit permit" first.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C6" CUSERID="U280" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>By Swimming....</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C7" CUSERID="U281" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>swimming is the best way!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C8" CUSERID="U282" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yes. Qatar Airways do fly directly to Melbourne.
So many dumb / useless / unhelpful answers posted here... 
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C9" CUSERID="U11" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>the only way to get there is by plane.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C10" CUSERID="U283" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>try catching an airplane :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C11" CUSERID="U20" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>Da, he can drive all the way to Singapore, then get a ferry :o)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C12" CUSERID="U20" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>eihco - so many dumb QUESTIONS asked here!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q75_C13" CUSERID="U284" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: how can i travel from qatar to australia</CSubject>
		<CBody>u can go by car via old airport get dwn there nd go via plane via sky nd u vll reach ur destination :P</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q76" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2010-12-10 21:19:56" QUSERID="U285" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Reef ready fish tanks</QSubject>
	<QBody>Which are good fish/pet shops in Doha that would sell fish tanks, aquarium supplies and fish? (both salt water and fresh fish) Are there Aquarium social clubs in Doha?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q76_C1" CUSERID="U286" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>many fish pet shops around</CSubject>
		<CBody>many fish pet shops around Doha located in Al muntazah or Al Markhiah but the professional one is Aqua Art for both fresh/salt water fish. visit thier website: http://www.aquaart.com.qa/

i don't think there is any aquarium social club in Doha but if you knew any,please let me know.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q76_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Aquarium</CSubject>
		<CBody>You can find too many pet shops in souq waquf where you can buy these cheap.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q76_C3" CUSERID="U285" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thanks all, this is very</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks all, this is very helpful!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q76_C4" CUSERID="U131" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Live reefs not available in</CSubject>
		<CBody>Live reefs not available in Qatar. Not sure about Aqua Art.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q76_C5" CUSERID="U170" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I have a fully-equipped Jebo</CSubject>
		<CBody>I have a fully-equipped Jebo tank &amp; stand (black) that I'd like to sell in case anyone is interested.  It's either 180 or 240 litres, I think.  I set it up once but then had to move before I added any fish.  I was going to set it up as a heavily planted tank, so it comes with a cable heater, CO2 system, inline heater, Eheim filtration (in addition to the built-in filtration) etc.  PM me for details.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q77" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2009-11-16 15:16:21" QUSERID="U287" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Where to get Coconut, where they cut and give</QSubject>
	<QBody>Where to get Coconut, where they cut and give. In Lulu they have stopped cutting it. Any other place? Thanks</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q77_C1" CUSERID="U231" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where to get Coconut, where they cut and give</CSubject>
		<CBody>lu lu hyper market, mall round about.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q77_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where to get Coconut, where they cut and give</CSubject>
		<CBody>FAMILY FOODS,INDIAN SUPER MARKET,LULU</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q77_C3" CUSERID="U288" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where to get Coconut, where they cut and give</CSubject>
		<CBody>Lu Lu Gharafa still has this facility.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q78" QCATEGORY="Life in Qatar" QDATE="2009-11-22 20:01:22" QUSERID="U289" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="Yes">
	<QSubject>Mixed info re driving licence</QSubject>
	<QBody>Before everyone shouts at me - I did a search and the info seems to be a bit old.(2006-2007)
So at the risk of being ridiculed - can I just ask a simple question?

Can I rent a car with an international driving license while waiting for my residency permit? Even if I have been here longer than 7 days? 

Its all very confusing!

</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q78_C1" CUSERID="U290" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>RE: Mixed info re driving licence</CSubject>
		<CBody>I came to Qatar and rent a car with my International Driving license until my RP was ready,if u want I can give you the office name i rented the car from.

So irresponsible answers from the mentioned person should be ignored.

Good luck my friend , Enjoy Qatar it is a lovely country.  </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q78_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>RE: Mixed info re driving licence</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hello friend,you can rent a car no problem...
But becarefull with radars and traffic camera
s
Welcome to Qatar and enjoy its beauty.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q78_C3" CUSERID="U291" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>RE: Mixed info re driving licence</CSubject>
		<CBody>yes no problem. i used my international licence for 10 months with a rental. even had an accident and had no problem at traffic dept with that licence. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q78_C4" CUSERID="U292" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>RE: Mixed info re driving licence</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yes no problem, did exactly that when we arrived, but make sure you convert to a Qatari Driving license as soon as your RP is processed</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q79" QCATEGORY="Family Life in Qatar" QDATE="2012-02-01 08:48:10" QUSERID="U293" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Fee structure for the 4th child and above</QSubject>
	<QBody>Please share your experience:

If a person sending his 6 kids in a same school, what will be the fee for the 4th, 5th and 6th child. In some cases even more.

</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q79_C1" CUSERID="U293" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thanks a lot</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks a lot</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q80" QCATEGORY="Sightseeing and Tourist attractions" QDATE="2011-04-10 19:37:58" QUSERID="U294" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>when is the best time/month to reserve a ticket going to the philippines?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Dear QL'ers esp my kababayans,

My family and I are planning of taking one month vacation to the Philippines this coming December. My question is, is there a specific month where booking reservations are cheaper? Can you also suggest a travel agency or an airline?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q80_C1" CUSERID="U295" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: when is the best time/month to reserve a ticket going...</CSubject>
		<CBody>..from experience though, early reservation will give you lower costs..and try to avoid pinas during vacations and pinas holidays...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q80_C2" CUSERID="U296" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: when is the best time/month to reserve a ticket going...</CSubject>
		<CBody>you have to get a december reservation in qatar airways before the month of november so you can get a cheaper price. </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q81" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2012-11-14 14:55:35" QUSERID="U37" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Which is best driving school in Doha,Qatar?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Which is best driving school in Doha,Qatar?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q81_C1" CUSERID="U297" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which is best driving school in Doha,Qatar?</CSubject>
		<CBody>please call me at 66505239 im mohamed hassan i work in raya driving school call me and i will arrange you excellent instructor
documents required :
Eye Test Report
Copy of ID or Visa Copy
Copy of Computer Number
Copy of Sponsor ID
4 Photos Passport

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q81_C2" CUSERID="U298" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which is best driving school in Doha,Qatar?</CSubject>
		<CBody>karwa</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q81_C3" CUSERID="U299" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which is best driving school in Doha,Qatar?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Al Rayah Driving School 

Nr Old Traffic Dept,
Frij Bin Omran,
Doha-Qatar

Tel :44877700
 I GOT LICENSE IN FIRST CHANCE. ITS EXCELLENT.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q81_C4" CUSERID="U300" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which is best driving school in Doha,Qatar?</CSubject>
		<CBody>karwa is best. as the strickness level is comparatively low</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q81_C5" CUSERID="U301" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which is best driving school in Doha,Qatar?</CSubject>
		<CBody>so dont worry , there is no any best in world. best this word should make by you . i m recommending gulf driving school will be good for you . i also got licence from there</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q81_C6" CUSERID="U302" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which is best driving school in Doha,Qatar?</CSubject>
		<CBody>How much it will cost for driving lesson?</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q82" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2010-11-14 09:37:18" QUSERID="U303" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Anyone on  Atkins Diet? Show us some hands!</QSubject>
	<QBody>Is anyone out there on an Atkins Diet?  I would like to know what you are currently eating!  

It a bit thinner now but i'm tired of eating chicken all the time.  I want to eat something tastier.  I know i'm allowed to eat a lot of other foods, so maybe you can help me out with your suggestions?

What's your no-carb recipe?

</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Well,i never tried getting so</CSubject>
		<CBody>Well,i never tried getting so fat and too skinny in my entire life.maybe it's an advantage that I don't like to eat something sweet. I eat chocolates once for two months or nothing at all. I just don't like it. I do walk sometimes whenever I get the chance. I eat not too small not too plenty..but my weight is the same. I guess my physique is really like this..But sometimes, i'd still want to lose a few pounds but my friends are telling me no need to lose anything..they tell me i'm getting paranoid sometimes..:(</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C2" CUSERID="U304" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>PS</CSubject>
		<CBody>You've never had kids right? lol..wait till you get preggers,habibthy!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C3" CUSERID="U47" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Fatimah - dont scare the poor</CSubject>
		<CBody>Fatimah - dont scare the poor thing...:P</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C4" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>dean.,I'm doing that the</CSubject>
		<CBody>dean.,I'm doing that the whole month of ramadan..It's great..Hope i'll get the chance again this coming eid,since I'm very occupied during work days and my work is up to 8pm..I'm always tired after work..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C5" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Yes fathimah,i never had</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yes fathimah,i never had kids,i'm not married and I'm still 20,mybe u r right,but my mom has the same physique as me after having 3 kids,i hope I'd be like her too someday..now,i still have little baby fats,i want to get rid of this.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C6" CUSERID="U305" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>You might have a heart attack</CSubject>
		<CBody>You might have a heart attack due to high amount of colesterol in blood.  Scientifically not good.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C7" CUSERID="U304" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>PS</CSubject>
		<CBody>your mom's among the privileged few!Baby fat is easy to loose compared to post pregnancy..Been there,done that =D</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C8" CUSERID="U303" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I don't know if you guys have</CSubject>
		<CBody>I don't know if you guys have read the article in the local english newspaper about some scientific findings that exercising is actually not the key to being skinny....I think that's bull, though.  

And anyway, scientists always scares me.  Them and their "findings".  

I do try to get exercise when I can, which is not a lot of times since i'm soooo busy lately.  If I can't do that, I go do Atkins.  I loooove eating, and i get so guilty that I have to diet after.  It's like a yo-yo diet.  Not good, I know, but what do I do when I don't have time for exercise?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C9" CUSERID="U306" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Ericdiver</CSubject>
		<CBody>I have found that Atkins in Qatar is really difficult... I lost over 50kgs on it and kept it off for 3 years (including 2.5years in Qatar) - then about 2 years ago, I just couldn't contain myself with all the good food - hummous, arabic bread, naan, butter chicken... etc... 

Techincally, I shouldn't have had a much of a problem - you can eat kebab with Rocket leaves and onions - or in salad - chicken doesn't have to be your only option.

Brunch at a Hotel on Sundays is brilliant - Berries, eggs and turkey/beef bacon, sausages, meat - thats all allowed.

What about making a smoothie of cream, berries and ice? 

Omelettes with mushrooms, greem peppers, diced chicken and cheeze....

There are lots of choices....

Have you seen this....

http://www.atkins.com/Program/low-carb-online-tools.aspx

There is a tab that will take you to meal plans and recipes.... try it:-)

You have just inspired me to start again....</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C10" CUSERID="U303" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Xena, thanks!</CSubject>
		<CBody>Wow, 50 kgs!  I don't think I inspire you...I think it is the other way around!  Thanks for sharing. :)   

From what I know, I'm not allowed to eat fruits.  Berries are fruits, right?  I'm still in induction phase, sorta.  I'm at it for almost 2 weeks now, and believe you me, I lost almost 3 kilos already!  It works, it works, it works people!

Ok, after the induction phase then I can start introducing carbs in my diet...by now i've no appetite for carbs, really.  I've lost it couple of days ago.  I'm just bored with the same old food that's all.

I guess my problem is i'm too tired to prepare something new and something on my own.  Lazy, lazy, lazy.  Eating out is a pain, since if you eat steaks (which I loooove) you get carbs as side dish.  I don't want to be tempted!  Quickest way is the good ol' chicken.  I shouldn't complain I know.  I'm switching to kebab.  

Thanks for the tips, i'm going to try out your suggestions!

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C11" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>50 Kgs! Thats like a whole</CSubject>
		<CBody>50 Kgs! Thats like a whole adult female!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C12" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Its impossible to follow a diet right through your life...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Its impossible to follow a diet right through your life...

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C13" CUSERID="U307" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Its impossible for me to</CSubject>
		<CBody>Its impossible for me to follow a diet right through the day JM ;)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C14" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Exercise is definitely the</CSubject>
		<CBody>Exercise is definitely the key.  I used to work out for an hour and a half 5 days a week and was skinny as a rail. Used to eat &amp; drink whatever I wanted and wouldn't gain a pound.  Met my husband and changed jobs, suddenly the workout time disappears and 2 years later here I am 20kg heavier and struggling to lose it, despite trying every diet in the book.  Exercise, Exercise, Exercise! </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C15" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>The main reason is the person is eating more</CSubject>
		<CBody>The main reason is the person is eating more than the body requires.... 
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C16" CUSERID="U304" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Tried an Atkins inspired diet..</CSubject>
		<CBody>but found it too depressing. I just did the carb curfew thingy and still do it for maintaining my weight, so welcome all low carb food suggestions. And yes it does make ordering food from restos real hard after 5pm =(</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C17" CUSERID="U48" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Never tried any diet, never</CSubject>
		<CBody>Never tried any diet, never will....I "live to Eat" :-)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C18" CUSERID="U304" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Agree with Dean..</CSubject>
		<CBody>Ultimately calorie counting will be anyones best bet.Its actually quite easy once you get a hang of it. And ofcourse exercise.On that note right now the weather is just awesome for evening walks! </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C19" CUSERID="U307" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Looks like I am doomed to be</CSubject>
		<CBody>Looks like I am doomed to be chubby then. If loosing weight means eating less and exercising I am sc***ed. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C20" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>He was slim because he was</CSubject>
		<CBody>He was slim because he was sick.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C21" CUSERID="U307" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>LP that's what happens when</CSubject>
		<CBody>LP that's what happens when you watch too many episodes of Friends </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C22" CUSERID="U308" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Eat Eggs</CSubject>
		<CBody>I was/am on Atkins quite frequently and lost weight also. But I found some problems like getting hyper on staff/customers, not been able to talk much etc etc. So I dont observe atkins regularly. May be two weeks on atkins and then break for some days/week and then again on atkins.

Yes atkins certainly helped me in loosing weight . Foods you can include (apart from chicken) is eggs ( all type), zero cola, bottle gourd, egg plant, okra,cheese, fish, tuna, salads. One thing more is&gt;&gt;&gt; lime juice once in day (especially in morning before food). This is not recommended in Atkins coz of bit high in carb but it help in making your food balance to more alkaline compared to acidic food. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C23" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Good for me. I don't even</CSubject>
		<CBody>Good for me. I don't even know what you're talking about, TB.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C24" CUSERID="U307" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Watch too many episodes of</CSubject>
		<CBody>Watch too many episodes of Friends and you become sick. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C25" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thanks for the info waliams!</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks for the info waliams!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C26" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I don't watch 'episodes', TB.</CSubject>
		<CBody>I don't watch 'episodes', TB. Only full length movies.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C27" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Accepted, TB.</CSubject>
		<CBody>Accepted, TB.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C28" CUSERID="U309" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>eh ? 
When ever i am in love,</CSubject>
		<CBody>eh ? 

When ever i am in love, i feel like eating more and more to make LOVE.....:(</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C29" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>if it's true then i think</CSubject>
		<CBody>if it's true then i think I've never been in love.:P</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C30" CUSERID="U47" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>gosh rizku - whatever</CSubject>
		<CBody>gosh rizku - whatever</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C31" CUSERID="U47" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>lol TB....
on a more serious</CSubject>
		<CBody>lol TB....

on a more serious note...no diet will work without exercise. at the end of the day you need to move those muscles and do some exercise.....

you can either walk or jog or anything u r comfy doing but u have to get a move on. alongwith exercise a diet thats fat free and sugar free helps a lot......</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C32" CUSERID="U23" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>oh geez, you need to</CSubject>
		<CBody>oh geez, you need to exercise!?! :P</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C33" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Another alternative would be</CSubject>
		<CBody>Another alternative would be to use your brain excessively. It will burn calories like hell. (Proven in many experiments).</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C34" CUSERID="U307" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Didn't Atkins die grossly</CSubject>
		<CBody>Didn't Atkins die grossly overweight?   </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C35" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I tried it and I lost weight</CSubject>
		<CBody>I tried it and I lost weight at first but then just plateaued and didn't lose anymore and the moment you go off it you gain the weight back right away. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C36" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Make love, don't eat. Simple</CSubject>
		<CBody>Make love, don't eat. Simple as that.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C37" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>LP eating is there...</CSubject>
		<CBody>LP eating is there... in the foreplay... how can one abstain?!! </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C38" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>LP,is ur suggestion proven &amp;</CSubject>
		<CBody>LP,is ur suggestion proven &amp; tested?LOL..

Ohh,I love eating chicken all the time,so I'd stick to chicken.haha

just watch what u eat..check the calories all the time,eat healthy foods,&amp; exercise of course,Following LP's tip is up to u:)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C39" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Trust me, jack. When you're</CSubject>
		<CBody>Trust me, jack. When you're in love you lose appetite.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q82_C40" CUSERID="U307" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Camels... they are</CSubject>
		<CBody>Camels... they are lightweights compared to me ;)</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q83" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2009-12-25 22:08:10" QUSERID="U37" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Business in Qatar</QSubject>
	<QBody>What are the advantages of starting a business in Qatar than in other countries?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C1" CUSERID="U12" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Victoria Secret and Ann</CSubject>
		<CBody>Victoria Secret and Ann Summers would do nice business here..

-----------------
"HE WHO DARES WINS"
Derek Edward Trotter</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C2" CUSERID="U310" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Finally someone with good</CSubject>
		<CBody>Finally someone with good subject to discus, thank you fembot

I tried to invest three times in Qatar, the regulation here are too complicated if I want to put it in a sentence then it is as following:

(Contacts and relationship is key for success in Qatar)

I dont know when those people who are responsible for setting up the process and procedures will realize that attracting investments to Qatar is not just by dropping the taxes 10%, no there are many other elements that should be considered 
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C3" CUSERID="U311" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Hasan, Qtr, taxes are not</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hasan, Qtr, taxes are not just dropped to 10%, but infact new taxes are introduced such as with holding taxes,


guess in longer run, eventually goverment may collect more taxes by introduction of new taxes.

ALLAH HU AKBAR - GOD IS GREAT</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C4" CUSERID="U312" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>this is not true, u have no</CSubject>
		<CBody>this is not true, u have no idea how much it is difficult to start a new business in any other country...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C5" CUSERID="U313" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Never ever think of starting</CSubject>
		<CBody>Never ever think of starting a business in Qatar. I know I sound stupid. But believe me. The rules are one hell of sucking rules. If you go to the government office one day they will say one thing and second day they will say they dont want what they said on 1st day. I have been trying to setup an organization here for the past 4 months. No luck at all. And believe me, they want only want MNC to come to Doha. Im quiting the idea of setting up business here and go somewhere else. Freaking government officials and they F***ing rules. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C6" CUSERID="U314" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>shaheka has a point, either</CSubject>
		<CBody>shaheka has a point, either you have a strong wealthy well known sponsor or just find a MNC to support you.

Yalla!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C7" CUSERID="U315" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>It is true that the rules</CSubject>
		<CBody>It is true that the rules are not clearly set out even we Qataris had trouble sometimes with them but if you have a Qatari partner/sponsor with good experience you can have your business up and running in a few months.. depending of course on the type of business and availability of the premises, manpower, resources etc..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C8" CUSERID="U316" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>i dont think businessmen or</CSubject>
		<CBody>i dont think businessmen or ladies chat in here..

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C9" CUSERID="U317" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>king_qatar, excuse moi?</CSubject>
		<CBody>king_qatar, excuse moi?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C10" CUSERID="U316" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>really
i never met</CSubject>
		<CBody>really
i never met businessmen online
what u do  pittstop</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C11" CUSERID="U315" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Why not king-qatar? We own</CSubject>
		<CBody>Why not king-qatar? We own our time more than govt employees!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C12" CUSERID="U317" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>king_qatar, what difference</CSubject>
		<CBody>king_qatar, what difference would it make? LOL -- I'm an employee, a business owner, and a student.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C13" CUSERID="U315" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>No qatarisun I'm 100%</CSubject>
		<CBody>No qatarisun I'm 100% Qataria..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q83_C14" CUSERID="U318" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I believe that Qatar now in</CSubject>
		<CBody>I believe that Qatar now in its best state for starting a business than it has ever been.

I also believe Qatar has advantages over many other countires in terms of business especially in terms of tax and charges. 

The only thing holding me from starting a business is the good idea which I am seriously searching for.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q84" QCATEGORY="Advice and Help" QDATE="2010-09-02 09:51:06" QUSERID="U319" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="Unsure">
	<QSubject>Canon Dealer / supplier in Washington</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hello QL friends,

Does any one have any information of a well reputed Canon Camera's Dealer/Supplier in Washington?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q84_C1" CUSERID="U319" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>well as we all know tht the</CSubject>
		<CBody>well as we all know tht the prices here are way to expensive thn in US, that is the onl reason i was looking out for a dealer in Washington, i was in touch with a dealer in NY who is also accosiated with Amazon, who had given me a good price for the camera and the lense, but the only problem is tht i am bit nervous in having it shipped out via courier, but then when a friend of mine told me tht he is flying to washington and if i cud find a reputed dealer in there he could pick it up for me and for sure will be cheaper as i can save on the customs duty and the courier charges.

That is the only reason.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q84_C2" CUSERID="U20" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>s_isale - I thought the</CSubject>
		<CBody>s_isale - I thought the request was quite straight forward.
saurabh - See my reply above.
Blood - helpful as ever.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q84_C3" CUSERID="U319" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>thank you, Blood, can you</CSubject>
		<CBody>thank you, Blood, can you please give me little more detail, as i mentioned above:

"Blood, can you let me know where excatly are you talking abt, and yes getting a discount is always good."</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q84_C4" CUSERID="U319" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>baldrick, it was really</CSubject>
		<CBody>baldrick, it was really helpfull, i do have tow address now and will pass it over to a friend of mine, but before i do tht i'll call up their office in US and get all the details.

Thank you for the help.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q84_C5" CUSERID="U320" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Actually </CSubject>
		<CBody>I thought this was some kind of a joke, the south pole is very far away for us to buy a camera delivering it to Qatar would really cost more than the camera itself, come on guys you made me feel guilty. My bad. :(</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q84_C6" CUSERID="U319" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>No issues, blood, atleast you</CSubject>
		<CBody>No issues, blood, atleast you ere kind enough to reply back to the post.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q84_C7" CUSERID="U20" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Blood, the problem is that</CSubject>
		<CBody>Blood, the problem is that for high end cameras, it's still cheaper  including delivery to get them shipped from USA, than it is to buy them here.

I bought my 5D on holiday in KL and a friends 7D in HK - they both worked out about 1/2 price compared to Doha</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q84_C8" CUSERID="U320" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>i can tell </CSubject>
		<CBody>About the south pole dealer if interested, I even might be able to get a special discount too.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q85" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2012-12-10 21:50:21" QUSERID="U321" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Hair Bun Donut Ring Sponge Shaper Maker</QSubject>
	<QBody>any idea where to get/buy a hair bun donut ring sponge around Doha? couldnt find one at Villagio. thanks!</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q85_C1" CUSERID="U251" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Yes, at Nazih beauty supply,</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yes, at Nazih beauty supply, on Salwa road.
But, you can make your own too!
Just take a sock, cut off the toe part, and roll it into a ring...viols, a doughnut!
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q85_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Get them at the wearhouse in</CSubject>
		<CBody>Get them at the wearhouse in old airport area.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q85_C3" CUSERID="U321" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>mooorning!</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks guys! y'all rock! and oh nomerci will try that one :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q85_C4" CUSERID="U251" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>blosgirl, you can search on</CSubject>
		<CBody>blosgirl, you can search on line for : "sockbun" there are several youtube videos that show you how to make on and how to use it!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q85_C5" CUSERID="U321" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>superb! cheers!</CSubject>
		<CBody>superb! cheers!</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q86" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2010-09-01 11:39:50" QUSERID="U322" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Blackberry Apps Blocked?</QSubject>
	<QBody>I'm looking at buying a Blackberry, but have heard a lot of stories about QTel restrictions.  Does QTel block the downloading of applications?  Some, many, all?

Thanks!

Max</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q86_C1" CUSERID="U26" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>did you hear anything about</CSubject>
		<CBody>did you hear anything about BB restrictions in Qatar?</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q87" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2009-04-26 17:11:00" QUSERID="U323" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Where can I find Japanese style wears in Doha</QSubject>
	<QBody>School teacher asked the children to come with Japanese cloth and food for a party. any idea where they can be??
thanks in advance..</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q87_C1" CUSERID="U324" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can I find Japanese style wears in Doha</CSubject>
		<CBody>available at splash in centrepoint and city center,just ask for salesman,the stores name is KINOBI,i`m not sure if u r looking for a traditional dress or just a japanese fashion,coz they dont hav traditional dress its only for fashion...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q87_C2" CUSERID="U323" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can I find Japanese style wears in Doha</CSubject>
		<CBody>thanks dear.. I will go tomorrow maybe I find something interesting</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q87_C3" CUSERID="U325" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can I find Japanese style wears in Doha</CSubject>
		<CBody>i wonder, how kids are looking with Japenese dress..  :D</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q88" QCATEGORY="Life in Qatar" QDATE="2009-04-14 01:28:11" QUSERID="U326" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>What is Doha Rocks?</QSubject>
	<QBody>I noticed many cars with the sticker "Doha Rocks" on it. What does Doha Rocks mean?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q88_C1" CUSERID="U327" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What is Doha Rocks?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Its a new cafe that is gonna open near the pizza hut...near the airport.There used to be a cafeteria called samco,they closed it down. Doha rocks have taken over it.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q88_C2" CUSERID="U328" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What is Doha Rocks?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Doha Rocks Cafe is opening soon at Airport Signal. Doha Rocks Cafe will be one of the most happening joints in town. It is going to be one of its kind in Doha as with all of their international cafe's across the world. You can enjoy free WiFi and make your meetings and leisure worth it. Doha Rocks Cafe ambience is uncomparable. Let us wait for the opening. They have an online presence at www.doharockscafe.co...


</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q88_C3" CUSERID="U20" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What is Doha Rocks?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Doha Rocks are things found in the Doha Desert ;oS</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q88_C4" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What is Doha Rocks?</CSubject>
		<CBody>It's the place Bob Dylan refers to when he sings:" Everybody must get stoned."</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q88_C5" CUSERID="U329" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What is Doha Rocks?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Is it kind of Hard Rock Cafe or something? But I've noticed they were saying its good for kids. Strange name for a place like that, isn't it? anyways, any clue when its gonna get opened?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q88_C6" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What is Doha Rocks?</CSubject>
		<CBody>hey Clement, could bea a place equally enjoyable for kids too. Just wait a see dude.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q88_C7" CUSERID="U330" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What is Doha Rocks?</CSubject>
		<CBody>DOHA ROCKS?? hahahaha funny name for a cafe.Im sure its gonna be as boring as a sleeping pill..zzzzzzz!!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q88_C8" CUSERID="U330" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What is Doha Rocks?</CSubject>
		<CBody>oops!! i already fell asleep! </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q88_C9" CUSERID="U331" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What is Doha Rocks?</CSubject>
		<CBody>If you goto the corniche, you will find these little pebbles close to the sea. I think Doha Rocks is a subtle reference to them.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q88_C10" CUSERID="U332" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What is Doha Rocks?</CSubject>
		<CBody>whatta wierd name for a cafe "doha rocks"
we dont've such cafes in the madagascar.
ahh i get it ..u gotta say the order like "one kappuccino on the rocks" haha..do i get an iPod now.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q89" QCATEGORY="Sightseeing and Tourist attractions" QDATE="2011-05-08 16:24:46" QUSERID="U333" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>What are the requirements for Road trip to Dubai?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi, 
I am planning a road trip to Dubai. since I already have a Qatari RP do I need a UAE visa? If so what is the procedure for obtaining it? Also what is the procedure for getting Road permit for Saudi Arabia?

Regards 

MN</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q89_C1" CUSERID="U334" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What are the requirements for Road trip to Dubai?</CSubject>
		<CBody>U need to have the following:

1. If u have Qatar Visa as a professional (engineer, architect etc) u get an on arrival visa in UAE/Dubai
2. U need to have Saudi double entry and exit visa, enquire with the embassy and find out if there are agent who facilitate the process.
3. Dont carry books, music-movies CDs', or anything non-islamic through Saudi Arabia. This stuff would be seized or u'll wait a long time till they verify the contents before they allow u to pass.
4. Dubai / UAE visa can be obtained at the Saudi / UAE border at Sila


</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q89_C2" CUSERID="U20" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What are the requirements for Road trip to Dubai?</CSubject>
		<CBody>First rule of getting through Saudi is to be MALE :o(</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q89_C3" CUSERID="U44" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: What are the requirements for Road trip to Dubai?</CSubject>
		<CBody>this is wedely discussed subject in QL, just in the search box put dubai by road, u will find plenty of tips / discussion forums, which are really useful</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q90" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2008-12-29 12:29:23" QUSERID="U335" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>House Rents</QSubject>
	<QBody>Can somebody advise me that how owners charge house rents in Doha-Qatar i.e. monthly or quarterly or annually etc?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q90_C1" CUSERID="U335" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: House Rents</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks guys 4 ur response</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q91" QCATEGORY="Beauty and Style" QDATE="2011-05-07 14:25:54" QUSERID="U336" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>can anyone suggest a good Dermatologist in Doha?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hello i just want to know how i can remove pimples scars from my face. It was there since childhood.Can anyone suggest me a good Dermatologist and please mention the phone number and cost of treatment.whether they cost huge amount?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q91_C1" CUSERID="U337" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: can anyone suggest a good Dermatologist in Doha?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Well i have been to Al emadi Hospital they have quite a good dermatologist section.
New exacly what to prescribe and advise me.

Price wise i havent got a clue</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q91_C2" CUSERID="U338" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: can anyone suggest a good Dermatologist in Doha?</CSubject>
		<CBody>try to look in the directory for DR.Ghazi Clinic....he charge 200qr for consultation but i dont know how much for the treatment that your asking...try to call so that you will have an idea of the price...goodluck :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q91_C3" CUSERID="U339" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: can anyone suggest a good Dermatologist in Doha?</CSubject>
		<CBody>I heard that Royal Medical center has a good dermatologist named : Rasha el Assi , give it a try ! 
call them on : 44659492</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q92" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2011-01-22 16:08:25" QUSERID="U340" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Can we bring our 40 days old baby  with out a visa.</QSubject>
	<QBody>I am working as a technician in a private company and my wife is working as a nurse in hammed hospital. But both of us are in different sponsorship. Could you please advice, can we bring our baby(40 days old) without a visa and what are the documents required.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q92_C1" CUSERID="U341" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Can we bring our 40 days old baby  with out a visa.</CSubject>
		<CBody>you surely need a visa and since your wife is working in Hamad she can bring the baby on her sponsership.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q92_C2" CUSERID="U342" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Can we bring our 40 days old baby  with out a visa.</CSubject>
		<CBody>I think you can bring the baby within 40days why she did not deliver in Qatar she is a nurse. when come attached both salary certificate and a letter from our sponsor NOC that u can sponsor the baby.Please wait for more response.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q92_C3" CUSERID="U343" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Can we bring our 40 days old baby  with out a visa.</CSubject>
		<CBody>Well It is not possible to get your baby without a valid visa as you know now there are provisions for a passport to be made for a new born.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q92_C4" CUSERID="U344" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Can we bring our 40 days old baby  with out a visa.</CSubject>
		<CBody>yes dear,you can bring your baby without a visa upto 90 days old but with a valid passport.subjected your wife's visa is still active..after entering to qatar you have to process residense visa within one month. you need,birth certificate (attested by minstry of foreign affairs and qatar consulate in your country),sponsors(your wife) visa and id copies,bank statements (3mnths),residential contract copy,attested degree certificates(rarely asks)and of course photographs of baby. since your wife is not under your sponsorship,before proceeding check with her sponsor for additional requirements.good luck.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q92_C5" CUSERID="U345" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Can we bring our 40 days old baby  with out a visa.</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hi Shan

Yes you can bring your child , visa will get on arrival, i think now upto 60 days no visa need , u have to bring attested birth cirtificate together. after arrival within 7 days u have to report authority.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q93" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2011-04-28 11:49:10" QUSERID="U346" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Where can I find Betaine Hydrochloride(HCL)?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Im trying to find out where can I get this supplement. 
I called GNC, Khouloud pharmacy, Tylos pharmacy, and none have it.  HELP!</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q93_C1" CUSERID="U346" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>You dont have anything to do,</CSubject>
		<CBody>You dont have anything to do, do you?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q93_C2" CUSERID="U347" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>sister, TRY the malls like</CSubject>
		<CBody>sister, TRY the malls like CITY CENTRE, VILAGGIO. orELSE u just have to keep calling all the pharmacies.
here is the link with all the numbers u need to call. 

http://www.qtel.qa/ImpSearch.do?catList=7&amp;subList=4

GoodLuck !!
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q93_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>It's one of the most common</CSubject>
		<CBody>It's one of the most common medicines around but seem to have a shortage throughout Qatar at the moment. It happens to quite a lot of medicines here. I would persevere and keep trying smaller Pharmacies. Don't bother phoning, actually go in as half the time the staff won't understand and its easier just to say no. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q93_C4" CUSERID="U219" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>My wife is on these</CSubject>
		<CBody>My wife is on these supplements for low stomach acid, she has not joined me out here yet, but we were going to get them sent from the UK as we weren't sure if they are available here.
It might be worth trying the internet if you have a PO box that they can be sent to, when my wife ran out of them she found it helpful to eat an orange with a meal as this does increase the stomachs ability to break down the fats.
Don't use a lemon as these turn alkiline in the stomach and make the problem worse.
Good luck</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q94" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2011-01-02 11:57:23" QUSERID="U348" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Can a Qatari Man Marry an Asian Girl?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi Everyone!

Happy new year!

I'm just curious to ask if a Qatari man can marry non-Qatari lady? What are the procedures need some opinion QLs. Thank you in advance and God Bless.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C1" CUSERID="U349" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>bad idea...</CSubject>
		<CBody>bad idea...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>yup</CSubject>
		<CBody>he can</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>n if ur doing so</CSubject>
		<CBody>its ur life's first and last mistake </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C4" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>he can marry a british or</CSubject>
		<CBody>he can marry a british or american girl how much more an asian girl..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C5" CUSERID="U350" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Better ask your Qatari BF</CSubject>
		<CBody>Better ask your Qatari BF about this... he knows best...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C6" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>which asia?</CSubject>
		<CBody>middle east asia, southeast asia, or fareast asia..of corz yes he can..y not..money can buy all things anway..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C7" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Don't marry an Arab if you</CSubject>
		<CBody>Don't marry an Arab if you want to be happy.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C8" CUSERID="U325" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>yes, 4 times different</CSubject>
		<CBody>yes, 4 times different nationalities !</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C9" CUSERID="U351" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>He can  ? </CSubject>
		<CBody>they brough the world cup in here why can't he marry an Asian Girl .. :)
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C10" CUSERID="U352" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Asian wife</CSubject>
		<CBody>As a first wife it can be very difficult to get permission.
For second/third/fourth it is easier.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C11" CUSERID="U353" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>so it is better to remain as</CSubject>
		<CBody>so it is better to remain as a MISTRESS,as others think it is very bad to be a second wife.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C12" CUSERID="U353" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>at least u have the freedom ,</CSubject>
		<CBody>at least u have the freedom , and the wife has the rights ;)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C13" CUSERID="U354" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>another name...."seppukku"..</CSubject>
		<CBody>another name...."seppukku"..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C14" CUSERID="U349" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Hara-kiri Meaning and</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hara-kiri Meaning and Definition
(n.) Suicide, by slashing the abdomen, formerly practiced in Japan, and commanded by the government in the cases of disgraced officials; disembowelment; -- also written, but incorrectly, hari-kari.

http://thinkexist.com/dictionary/meaning/hara-kiri/</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C15" CUSERID="U354" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>means  "ceremonial suicide"</CSubject>
		<CBody>means  "ceremonial siucide"</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C16" CUSERID="U350" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>seppuku - Ritual suicide by</CSubject>
		<CBody>seppuku - Ritual suicide by disembowelment formerly practiced by Japanese samurai. Also called hara-kiri.

???</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C17" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Isn't every marriage a</CSubject>
		<CBody>Isn't every marriage a ceremonial suicide??</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C18" CUSERID="U355" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>marry me i have oil wells too</CSubject>
		<CBody> marry me i have oil wells too</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C19" CUSERID="U145" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Yes they can.
The man has to</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yes they can.

The man has to get permission from the government. this can be time consuming sometimes.  

The best option is to ask at Fanar or similar.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C20" CUSERID="U349" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>there is a temporary marriage</CSubject>
		<CBody>there is a temporary marriage here, it seems...but why waste life on temporary basis...

we become older everyday, depreciating everyday

bad idea...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C21" CUSERID="U353" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>vic</CSubject>
		<CBody>the funny thing is that if the word "temporary" included in marriage, the contract will be canceled.
temporary + contract of marriage = "not marriage,but...:P"</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C22" CUSERID="U349" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>bad idea...really
wait, take</CSubject>
		<CBody>bad idea...really

wait, take ur time...u will meet someone who will be willing to spend the rest of his life with you and love u sincerely.



 </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q94_C23" CUSERID="U354" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>yes....he can...the procedure</CSubject>
		<CBody>yes....he can...the procedure is known as "Harakiri' and it works both ways!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q95" QCATEGORY="Life in Qatar" QDATE="2010-06-07 17:47:40" QUSERID="U356" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Hamad Medical Corporation- Paramedic</QSubject>
	<QBody>I would like to know if there are any Expat EMT-Paramedics working for HMC? I have been offered a job and will start as soon as my Visa is approved. What are the standards of housing they supply? What are essentials to bring? My wife and I will both be working for HMC, both on Grade 112.
Any info will be appreciated...
Thanks  </QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q95_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Hamad Medical Corporation- Paramedic</CSubject>
		<CBody>Ive known they have alot of expats like filipino/indians paramedics in HMC and plus they provide good accommodation for their staff single or family status.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q95_C2" CUSERID="U357" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Hamad Medical Corporation- Paramedic</CSubject>
		<CBody>Depending on the grade and size of family they provide,definitely a decent furnished accomodation.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q95_C3" CUSERID="U358" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Hamad Medical Corporation- Paramedic</CSubject>
		<CBody>they provide decent accomodation 
u can take money and can stay outside 

</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q96" QCATEGORY="Moving to Qatar" QDATE="2010-07-15 06:43:27" QUSERID="U359" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Park House School - Buses</QSubject>
	<QBody>Does anyone know whether Park House School runs buses to pick up and drop off children ?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q96_C1" CUSERID="U360" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>No they don't</CSubject>
		<CBody>but there is a private company that does PHES run.  I can't remember the name of it but it may be on their website or call them a week before school starts to ask for the contact details.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q96_C2" CUSERID="U361" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>PHES buses</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hi tried to send you an email but failed miserably
Farhen Al- Sayed runs the buses 
email him on

farhanalsayed@hotmail.com

and he'll sort it out for you

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q96_C3" CUSERID="U362" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>d`ont think so ...:(</CSubject>
		<CBody>d`ont think so ...:(</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q97" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2009-12-09 09:38:52" QUSERID="U363" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="Yes">
	<QSubject>NEW Sewing Machine Wanted</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi

Am looking for a sewing machine (preferably BROTHERS or SINGER).
I searched a few shopping malls and almost all the malls have both BROTHERS and SINGER made in CHINA.....

Can some one help me locate a shop where i can get a sewing machine made anywhere else other than China!!
(People say Japan / Korea make are good..)

Cheers:)
Edd</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q97_C1" CUSERID="U147" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Unsure">
		<CSubject>I remember seeing a shop</CSubject>
		<CBody>I remember seeing a shop somewhere near to Doha City...
I think they are the dealers of Brother Sweing Machine...




&lt;a href="http://s434.photobucket.com/albums/qq67/formattedsoul/?action=view&amp;current=0003.gif" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i434.photobucket.com/albums/qq67/formattedsoul/0003.gif" border="0" alt="Photobucket"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q97_C2" CUSERID="U11" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>Yupe FS</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thats just on the Clock roundabout next to the Music Store.

&lt;img src="http://www.qatarliving.com/files/images/Da.gif"&gt;

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q97_C3" CUSERID="U363" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thanx FormattedSoul
Thanx</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanx FormattedSoul
Thanx DaRuDe.....
will check out...
hope i find one of my choice......other than chinese made....</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q97_C4" CUSERID="U363" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>anybody has anyother</CSubject>
		<CBody>anybody has anyother suggestions?
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q97_C5" CUSERID="U317" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Yes">
		<CSubject>Fredoni - Singer : Clock</CSubject>
		<CBody>Fredoni - Singer : Clock Roundabout</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q97_C6" CUSERID="U364" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>price plzz</CSubject>
		<CBody>how much r u selling ur sewing machine for?
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q98" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2011-01-29 09:59:40" QUSERID="U365" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>How many days does it take to have Family Visit Visa ?</QSubject>
	<QBody>How many days does it take to have Family Visit Visa ?

Is that the most quick way to bring my wife to doha?

Even she is canceled ; can she work again after i bring her with my sponsorship (as my wife)??

Thanks aLL</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q98_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: How many days does it take to have Family Visit Visa ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>same dayyyyyyyyyy</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q98_C2" CUSERID="U35" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: How many days does it take to have Family Visit Visa ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>2 working days if you submit all proper documents. She can come back under your sponsorship and work if she has got an NOC from her previous company.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q98_C3" CUSERID="U366" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: How many days does it take to have Family Visit Visa ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>All depends on your company PRO. If your PRO is smart enough hw can get in two days....</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q98_C4" CUSERID="U366" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: How many days does it take to have Family Visit Visa ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>All depends on your company PRO. If your PRO is smart enough hw can get in two days....</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q98_C5" CUSERID="U365" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: How many days does it take to have Family Visit Visa ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>so if she doesnt have NOC; she can not work??</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q98_C6" CUSERID="U367" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: How many days does it take to have Family Visit Visa ?</CSubject>
		<CBody>yes she must require an NOC from previous employer if she want to work, but anyhow on a family visit visa no body is allow to work.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q99" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2008-11-04 21:47:57" QUSERID="U170" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Can anyone recommend a painter?</QSubject>
	<QBody>The painter that our compound mgmt sent over was clearly gouging us - he wanted 1,500QR per room, which is more than it would cost in the U.S. .. .and I know the guys here are making much much less than the immigrant labor in Texas.

Any recommendations for someone who will do a good job for a fair price?

Thanks,

Expat Sueo</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q99_C1" CUSERID="U368" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Painting is very easy and a</CSubject>
		<CBody>Painting is very easy and a fun job to do. You can buy the paint at any Jotun shop, where they will mix it by computer to any shade you want. Then get some rollers and do it yourself. You will save a lot of money and you will feel so much better after you have completed the job. Really rewarding. I love painting my house and have done everything myself.
Aisha-Taweela
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q99_C2" CUSERID="U369" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>200Qr</CSubject>
		<CBody>is what we spent for each room. They are more than ripping you off. We went to Jotun (there is one in the same place as Party Kingdom near Jaidah Flyover) and bought the paint there and contracted with one of their workers.  He would come over at night after his regular job was done.  this was somewhat inconvenient, but he was good and cheap!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q99_C3" CUSERID="U170" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thanks, Aisha-Taweela &amp; deedee</CSubject>
		<CBody>I ended up finding someone to paint the three rooms for 1,000QR.  It's more than 200/room, but he paints for a number of people in the compound and brings his own supplies.

I need to scurry on over to pick up the paint tomorrow!

cheers,

Expat Sueo </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q99_C4" CUSERID="U170" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>haha kamranhassan!</CSubject>
		<CBody>Don't let me fool you. . .I'm blessed by plenty of bad luck as well.  I have more "strange bad luck stories" than you could possibly imagine!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q99_C5" CUSERID="U370" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Expat Sueo.</CSubject>
		<CBody>Dear ,


Than you should close to GOD always pray for your luck.
Its doest not matter.

I don't know anything about luck. I've never banked on it, and I'm afraid of people who do. 

Luck to me is something else; hard work and realizing what is opportunity and what isn't/

 When the good luck comes - ready to receive it.

Always count yourself in lucky persons..

Thanks</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q99_C6" CUSERID="U170" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>you were right on, SPEED</CSubject>
		<CBody>The person who came did it for 1,000QR and did a fantastic job.  The guy who wanted to do it for 4,500 must have been smoking something!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q99_C7" CUSERID="U370" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>U R</CSubject>
		<CBody>ALWYAS COUNT UR LIFE WITH SMILES...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q99_C8" CUSERID="U371" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>deedee</CSubject>
		<CBody> 
do u have phone number for guy who done ur painting,pm me thanks</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q99_C9" CUSERID="U372" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>painting cost is a tricky issue</CSubject>
		<CBody>the 200 and the 1500 sound logical. it really depends on the extent of work. it could be simple painting and applying one or two layers of normal paint. It could be also a complicated task which involve scraping, priming then doing several layers of paint.

===================================== http://www.qatarliving.com/node/58409 
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q100" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2009-11-10 10:14:37" QUSERID="U373" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>parking ticket - how much?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi guys

I just got a parking ticket :(  Does anyone know how much I'll have to pay?  Can't get into moi.gov.qa at the moment.

thanks</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q100_C1" CUSERID="U87" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>300QR plus 3 black points</CSubject>
		<CBody>300QR plus 3 black points deducted on your license


&lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;How far you go in life depends on you being tender with the young, compassionate with the aged, tolerant of the weak. Someday you will have been all of these.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q100_C2" CUSERID="U228" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Just QR 300/-</CSubject>
		<CBody>indirect tax....</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q100_C3" CUSERID="U373" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thanks guys.  Really pee'd</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks guys.  Really pee'd off now though.  </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q100_C4" CUSERID="U12" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Yep They pick and</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yep They pick and choose

-----------------
"HE WHO DARES WINS"
Derek Edward Trotter</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q100_C5" CUSERID="U374" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I heard u need to pay 500</CSubject>
		<CBody>I heard u need to pay 500 for that? not sure tho..
_______________________________________________________
"All those who believe in psycho kinesis, raise my hand."</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q100_C6" CUSERID="U375" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>@svelte</CSubject>
		<CBody>"Driving a vehicle loaded in such a way that it cause damage to people and surroundings" - this usually means speeding and it is caught by the radar at traffic lights if you cross the speed limit for that road. 
You can go to Traffic Dept at Old Airport or Madinat Khalifa  and request to see a video of the violation. Ur dad can tell if its his car and move accordingly. 
The place zones can often be misleading due to error in data entry. But timing will be accurate, only our minds play tricks on timings. 
Worth checking out the video than speculating. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q100_C7" CUSERID="U376" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>dear svelte ...</CSubject>
		<CBody>its happened with me once and they mention that driving a car which is above 50 meters or the level allowd in website and when i checked in arabic then i find out its a seat belt panelty ... when they enter in there system at traffic dept they enter in arabic and then system is translating in silly enligh option which is enterd already from there side at traffic dept.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q100_C8" CUSERID="U228" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>SS....</CSubject>
		<CBody>this comments appeared ONLY incase of speeding and caught by Radar (Salwa roads or Corniche, elsewhere)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q100_C9" CUSERID="U377" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>QR500. But then these LC's</CSubject>
		<CBody>QR500. But then these LC's are parked in the middle of the road waiting for groceries without any tickets issued</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q100_C10" CUSERID="U151" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>+3 points</CSubject>
		<CBody>+3 points </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q100_C11" CUSERID="U378" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I received</CSubject>
		<CBody>a ticket on line and I made a enquiry also online and explianed that I was at work at the time of the incident.
The violation disappeared.
Make sure you are inputting the proper type of license plate. Cars are private vehicles and trucks are private transportation, don't pay someone else's fine by accident, unless it's mine.


I don't think we need to do anything in the name of God, he's a big boy and can take of himself.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q101" QCATEGORY="Education" QDATE="2010-10-12 15:14:11" QUSERID="U379" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>I need the website of American academy school pls?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Any one known abt American Acadamy school ?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q101_C1" CUSERID="U157" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: I need the website of American academy school pls?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Did you try searching before posting???

Check the &lt;b&gt;&lt;a&gt;Search&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; results

http://www.qatarliving.com/search?cx=008937172676595728955%3A066rihafv68&amp;cof=FORID%3A11&amp;Q=american+Academy#1326

Regards!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q101_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: I need the website of American academy school pls?</CSubject>
		<CBody>WWW.AMERICANACADEMYSCHOOL.COM</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q101_C3" CUSERID="U379" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: I need the website of American academy school pls?</CSubject>
		<CBody>I google it be4 I post.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q101_C4" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: I need the website of American academy school pls?</CSubject>
		<CBody>They don't have one.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q102" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2010-03-18 08:29:14" QUSERID="U380" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>where can i do alter bottom of my jeans......?????help guys </QSubject>
	<QBody>hey...guys

i want to alter bottom of my jeans it is lil bit long...so i want exactly same as original one...if i go to any local tailor they do but not as the original...

if u cant see the end of jeans it looks kinda weird...i want it noticable. brands r Lee n Wrangler any showroom here if they do...plzz do let me know...ASAP guys ive to wear it on friday...!!</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q102_C1" CUSERID="U381" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: where can i do alter bottom of my jeans......????...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Alteration is done only when you buy a new jeans from the retailers.  Only option is to go to local tailors.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q102_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: where can i do alter bottom of my jeans......????...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Anyone needs help in altering their bottoms...contact me</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q102_C3" CUSERID="U380" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: where can i do alter bottom of my jeans......????...</CSubject>
		<CBody>once i gave my jeans to LEE..they did exactly original as i want...but in india.

now i bought jeans from this stupid LULU....i asked thm will guys do alteration like original one....they said no we do only local alteration. i dont wanna spoil my jeans on their hands....prob is i dont know where is LEE or Wrangler here in doha........if u guys know where is these showrooms let me know.

ive checked CC but dint find any LEE shop.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q102_C4" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: where can i do alter bottom of my jeans......????...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Jazz Your contact details please.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q102_C5" CUSERID="U262" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: where can i do alter bottom of my jeans......????...</CSubject>
		<CBody>wrongside,
To hell with ur thinking..I feel like to abuse u in the main forum..but i can't degrade myself for the people like u..take care of ur own sis n mom or other female members if they too go for alteration..shame on u!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q103" QCATEGORY="Family Life in Qatar" QDATE="2008-11-15 00:22:22" QUSERID="U382" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Starting nursery</QSubject>
	<QBody>We might be moving to Qatar next year, and I was wondering, I would like to have my kids in a nursery, can they start in the middle of the year, or do they have to wait until august?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q103_C1" CUSERID="U383" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>From what i know, Nurserys</CSubject>
		<CBody>From what i know, Nurserys are available all year round. If its a kindergarden, some close in summer . However some provide summer programs for the kids who stay in Doha, but you would need to register before the available positions fill up.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q103_C2" CUSERID="U382" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>If I get a job I need to</CSubject>
		<CBody>If I get a job I need to have my children in nurserys. Here in Norway both my children will be in a nurserys, we cant afford to live on one salery</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q103_C3" CUSERID="U383" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>you wont have any problem</CSubject>
		<CBody>you wont have any problem getting a nursery here for your child.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q103_C4" CUSERID="U384" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Cant afford?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Of course if you want to work, that's fine...  But as a European your husband should have gotten a salary package that can support a family.  If he didn't, you got taken advantage of.  </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q103_C5" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>USAexpat.....wrong</CSubject>
		<CBody>USAexpat.....wrong completely....thats not how it works.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q103_C6" CUSERID="U385" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>yes you</CSubject>
		<CBody>can send them in the midle of the year,most of the nurseries provide summer program ,and most of them start around 6 am or 6 :30 until 2, 3or 4 pm,the good ones are expensive around 1600 ,1800QR.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q103_C7" CUSERID="U382" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I think I have to wait until</CSubject>
		<CBody>I think I have to wait until we know if we are moving or not before I put the kids name on any lists. 

Im not sure if my husbands company are paying for nursery, I know they are paying for school, but not sure about nursery.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q104" QCATEGORY="Advice and Help" QDATE="2010-06-15 17:47:07" QUSERID="U386" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Serviced Apartments</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi,

Is anyone staying at serviced apartments? Which ones would you advise me? What are the rates for a 1 bedroom apartment in such places?

It would be of great help if anyone has info.

Thanx a lot.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q104_C1" CUSERID="U386" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thanx folks</CSubject>
		<CBody>I already checked out the classifieds. But is it always better to investigate through friends and people who already experienced all these :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q104_C2" CUSERID="U387" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>hi</CSubject>
		<CBody>hi we are having 1 bedroom fully furnished flat..with cleaning service..if you would like to view the apartment please mail me ..
thanx</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q104_C3" CUSERID="U388" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Qairawan_doha &amp; Samikhan222</CSubject>
		<CBody>Qairawan_doha &amp; Samikhan222 ,

Please describe the following items of your property:

Type:
Detailed Description:
Size:
Monthly Rent:
Location:
Contacts:


So your potential clients won't waste time if your advertised property does not meet their requirements</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q104_C4" CUSERID="U388" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>s_isale,
"Qatar Living</CSubject>
		<CBody>s_isale,

"Qatar Living Classifieds" are useless and mismanaged.

QL allows multiple post of the same add, in a very short time. 

You may get 1 add repeated 10 times in just a few hours!

That's why people try this way!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q104_C5" CUSERID="U387" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Its already there in the</CSubject>
		<CBody>Its already there in the classified ...please  have a look..or track me</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q104_C6" CUSERID="U389" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I am renting on room of a two</CSubject>
		<CBody>I am renting on room of a two bedroom service appartment .qr 1300. Contact me 3424079 if interested.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q104_C7" CUSERID="U390" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Need advice</CSubject>
		<CBody> 2 or 3days back i post an advertise bout a room for rent but it doesnt shows anything in the classified.please.... i need an advice.if i go to news paper agency quit expensive!thanks
</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q105" QCATEGORY="Education" QDATE="2009-09-26 13:01:39" QUSERID="U391" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="No">
	<QSubject>okay seriously, is there school tommorow?</QSubject>
	<QBody>everyone is sayin differen things, something about swine flu.. when will we find out?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q105_C1" CUSERID="U20" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: okay seriously, is there school tommorow?</CSubject>
		<CBody>have you tried ringing the school?
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q105_C2" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>RE: okay seriously, is there school tommorow?</CSubject>
		<CBody>The Ministry today decided that all private and public schools should not open before the 4th October. So, 4th Oct is the reopening day.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q105_C3" CUSERID="U196" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>RE: okay seriously, is there school tommorow?</CSubject>
		<CBody>I have been to my childrens school this morning and sure schools are not open until October 4, 2009.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q105_C4" CUSERID="U369" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>RE: okay seriously, is there school tommorow?</CSubject>
		<CBody>it depends on the school
Philipino schools started in June
American school started in Aug
British schools started in Sept.

Your question is too vague.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q105_C5" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>RE: okay seriously, is there school tommorow?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Tha schools will open in 4th of October.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q106" QCATEGORY="Salary and Allowances" QDATE="2012-07-22 14:44:25" QUSERID="U392" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Transport Planner Salary</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hey everyone,
Just curious if anyone knows the typical salary for a transport planner with 6 years experience working for an engineering consultancy in Qatar?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q106_C1" CUSERID="U393" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>approx 25k</CSubject>
		<CBody>25k per month QAR approx...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q106_C2" CUSERID="U394" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Should be in the range of 20k</CSubject>
		<CBody>Should be in the range of 20k to 30k, depending upon the educational qualification, previous experience &amp; the company .. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q106_C3" CUSERID="U392" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>qualifications</CSubject>
		<CBody>To help you out I have 6 years transport planning consulting experience plus two degrees in planning.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q106_C4" CUSERID="U394" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>You can ask for QR 30k+ ..</CSubject>
		<CBody>You can ask for QR 30k+ ..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q106_C5" CUSERID="U395" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Hi,
You have good experience,</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hi,

You have good experience, you will get about 20 to 30 k. know more please visit at http://zuby.in/

Thanks</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q106_C6" CUSERID="U396" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>traders insurance</CSubject>
		<CBody>Maybe you've just got a cracking deal on a car bought off eBay or Autotrader, the only hitch being that it is sitting in Mr. Jones' driveway over the other side of the country? Or, you need to get your non-runner moved from A to B? Whatever your reasons, finding a car transport company to get your pride and joy delivered is something that most of us encounter at some point. 
&lt;a href="traders insurance"&gt;http://www.motortradesinsurance.com&lt;/a&gt;</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q107" QCATEGORY="Cars" QDATE="2009-09-28 10:15:25" QUSERID="U397" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Which rental car company is best for price?</QSubject>
	<QBody>I'm looking for a small car and I accept limited mileage.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q107_C1" CUSERID="U398" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which rental car company is best for price?</CSubject>
		<CBody>AlMuftah Rent a car.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q107_C2" CUSERID="U399" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which rental car company is best for price?</CSubject>
		<CBody>Rayyan Car Rental ... they got Nissan Tiida if you are interested at 1600 - 1800 per month depending on your situation and how long are you planning to rent it.

Their service is good, if your car broke down they will send someone to fix it or help.

When it's time for service, you can call them and ask them to pass by your office to change the oil and clean the car then bring it back.

They are located in Al-Asmakh street ... close to crazy signal ...
 </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q107_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which rental car company is best for price?</CSubject>
		<CBody> 4 cheap &amp;  best 
1)TRUTH RENT A CAR 
2)POLYGON RENT A CAR
3)ORRY RENT A CAR</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q107_C4" CUSERID="U400" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which rental car company is best for price?</CSubject>
		<CBody>I am currently renting from Al Odeidly and they have reasonable rates. So far, i've had a good experience.

And the other companies that the other people suggested have good rates also...they look about right. Is just a matter of availability.

But careful with PETRA. They prices look good at first, but they get you at the end. I wouldnt recommend them.
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q107_C5" CUSERID="U401" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which rental car company is best for price?</CSubject>
		<CBody>try ureo dollar. you are renting their services not just the car. so cheap
4351397</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q108" QCATEGORY="Life in Qatar" QDATE="2009-02-28 20:11:10" QUSERID="U402" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>meeting expat young people</QSubject>
	<QBody>where is the best place to meet european-australian-american expats between 25-35 years old in doha?</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q108_C1" CUSERID="U403" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: meeting expat young people</CSubject>
		<CBody>Please don't mind HASSAN SHAIKH replies he is very Silly</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q108_C2" CUSERID="U53" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: meeting expat young people</CSubject>
		<CBody>I am silly. Are you not the one who wanted to know ahy Qatari wonem don't marry Moroccon men? And are you not the one who wanted to know how much any cell phone costs? Are you sure I am the one who is silly? </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q108_C3" CUSERID="U403" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: meeting expat young people</CSubject>
		<CBody>YEP YOU ARE THE SILLIEST EXPATRIATE IN QATAR ....YOU LACK RESPECT IN YOUR ANSWERS.
YOU DON T ANSWER TO GUIDE OR INFORM BUT RATHER TO DISTURB AND MOCK ON PEOPLE.
WAKE UP MAN AND GET THIS BEHAVIOUR CHANGED IN DUE TIME BEFORE YOU BEING SLAPPED ON YOUR FACE</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q109" QCATEGORY="Advice and Help" QDATE="2012-10-11 10:00:31" QUSERID="U404" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Doha Bank - E Remittance</QSubject>
	<QBody>Did anybody have an experience with Doha Bank - E Remittance (Online Banking). I want to know how reliable it's and how much time it takes to reach in India ICICI Bank NRI Account.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q109_C1" CUSERID="U405" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>does it provide best exchange</CSubject>
		<CBody>does it provide best exchange rate also when compared to exchange cells ?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q109_C2" CUSERID="U201" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>..</CSubject>
		<CBody>simple &amp; modernize , reliable way to move your fund overseas , advisable !! </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q109_C3" CUSERID="U406" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>caution</CSubject>
		<CBody>There are many news about money stolen from the people who used this mode .. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q109_C4" CUSERID="U406" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>take care .. all</CSubject>
		<CBody>Although phishing has become fairly well known, the scam continues to be a successful and widely used as a method of stealing bank credentials and other personal information.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q109_C5" CUSERID="U404" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thanks all for your replies</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks all for your replies and advices, InshAllah I will take care of phishing, scams etc., :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q109_C6" CUSERID="U407" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Doha Bank</CSubject>
		<CBody>E-remittance is OK for India but not allowed for USA.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q109_C7" CUSERID="U408" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Transfer Charge..</CSubject>
		<CBody>Dears what about the Transaction charge/Fund transfer charge..?</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q110" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2008-12-16 11:26:24" QUSERID="U409" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>my-gym</QSubject>
	<QBody>i have been told that franchisee of my-gym ,is in doha. anybody know about their preshchool</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q110_C1" CUSERID="U369" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>preschool</CSubject>
		<CBody>There are a lot of good preschools in Doha.  At the bottom right hand side of your screen is a Guide to Qatar.  click on the Qatar schools database and go from there.  also the Marhaba book that you can buy at Jarir bookstore &amp; all grocery stores have a great list as well.  I would take into account where you live (you will not want to drive across town in doha traffic if you can help it!) and your budget.  Good luck</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q110_C2" CUSERID="U410" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Nursery Preschool - Petits Pas</CSubject>
		<CBody>There is a great one called Petits Pas by TV roundabout.
The curriculum is French with some english and it's very nice and they do activities in the afternoon for kids, painting, gym etc.. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q110_C3" CUSERID="U411" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>it is opposite the exhibition centre</CSubject>
		<CBody>and comes under my centre, it's a yellow coloured villa</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q110_C4" CUSERID="U409" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>k</CSubject>
		<CBody>do they have a preschoolis it any good, </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q111" QCATEGORY="Beauty and Style" QDATE="2009-04-06 10:22:49" QUSERID="U412" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Beauty Salon</QSubject>
	<QBody>Pls recomend a good ladies beauty salon,, in doha.how is salon in Lulu hyper market?? I need a place for a clean up and for a hair cut.</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q111_C1" CUSERID="U413" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Beauty Salon</CSubject>
		<CBody>Try Happy Women Salon, near Diamond Hotel...
their offer a very affordable prices for all treatments. look for Ms. Fina at tel #4365121/6819313 for more inquiries</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q111_C2" CUSERID="U414" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Beauty Salon</CSubject>
		<CBody>You should stop by our salon (J&amp;J's Secret Of Beauty) located behind Carrefour at Landmark. We have a great Korean hairdresser who graduated from a Beautician College and has nearly 10 years of experience, she's amazing!! If interested call us at 421-8404.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q111_C3" CUSERID="U415" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Beauty Salon</CSubject>
		<CBody>Hi! Be Bloom Beauty Center &amp; Spa will be the best suit for you, they are best for hair cutting. I've been their 2 weeks ago and I done my hair cut, I really love it!!!!</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q112" QCATEGORY="Environment" QDATE="2010-12-08 11:17:12" QUSERID="U37" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>New to Qatar</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hy Every one, 
              I'm a Hardware Engineer, bt i got good chance in Contracting field, I'm really new to Qatar, I wanna know some thing more about Qatar, So Pls Any Advice?...... :) 
will be appreciate...... 
Thanks a lot in Advance.... :)</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q112_C1" CUSERID="U23" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>joan, what kind of sports do</CSubject>
		<CBody>joan, what kind of sports do you play?</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q113" QCATEGORY="Visas and Permits" QDATE="2009-07-29 10:32:56" QUSERID="U416" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>New Born Child Sponsorship.</QSubject>
	<QBody>Just want to know, my wife is about to give birth this coming October, both of us were under our company sponsor and currently working in Qatar. Is it okay if one of us will sponsor our new born child or both of us?
What is the procedure? Requirements? thanks</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q113_C1" CUSERID="U417" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: New Born Child Sponsorship.</CSubject>
		<CBody>If your wife will deliver here in Qatar:
	Get birth certificate from NHA.
	Issue passport from your embassy.
	Send it to immigration with your &amp; your wife passport copy, ID copy and your original ID.(400 QR)

If your wife will deliver out side Qatar:
	Baby will get visa in arrival.
	Send your babys passport to medical commission with 100 QR for issuing him/ her medical receipt.
	Send it to immigration with your &amp; your wife passport copy, ID copy and your original ID. (400 QR)

Regards,
Basem 
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q113_C2" CUSERID="U418" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: New Born Child Sponsorship.</CSubject>
		<CBody>hi,
you could apply in labour dept for the visa. the infant with less than 3 months old need not require visa to enter into qatar.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q113_C3" CUSERID="U232" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: New Born Child Sponsorship.</CSubject>
		<CBody>Either one of you can sponsor, no issues, check with your PRO about the formalities.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q113_C4" CUSERID="U419" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: New Born Child Sponsorship.</CSubject>
		<CBody>It'll be easiest if the man sponsors the child - less questions and raised eyebrows.

Birth certificate from Hamad/NHA, passport from Embassy, then get the RP.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q114" QCATEGORY="Computers and Internet" QDATE="2010-10-24 16:33:56" QUSERID="U420" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Where can i buy a IMEI Number for china mobile???</QSubject>
	<QBody>Where can i buy a IMEI Number for china mobile using for India, ????. pls help me
Thanks n Regards

</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q114_C1" CUSERID="U421" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where can i buy a IMEI Number for china mobile???</CSubject>
		<CBody>careefaur,street no-18,central bazar,north beijing,china.</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q115" QCATEGORY="Life in Qatar" QDATE="2010-02-04 14:44:22" QUSERID="U422" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="No">
	<QSubject>Can i work in qatar under my fathers sponsorship?</QSubject>
	<QBody>i want to work in qatar for few months and then i may go outside qatar for my further studies ..........i applied here in some companies but they will give me job only if i change my sponsor............................

is dere any solution fo this </QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q115_C1" CUSERID="U423" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>RE: Can i work in qatar under my fathers sponsorship?</CSubject>
		<CBody>technically you can't work under your father's sponsorship
But you can transfer your sponsorship to whichever employer even if your employer does not have a visa of your specific nationality, its easier that way
But if and when you do a transfer, you have to be careful because specific nationalities such as Jordanian for instance can be denied a transfer in which case you may end up in trouble...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q115_C2" CUSERID="U424" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Can i work in qatar under my fathers sponsorship?</CSubject>
		<CBody>concentrate on your studies and when you finish, it's time to find work suitable for you.

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q115_C3" CUSERID="U425" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="No">
		<CSubject>RE: Can i work in qatar under my fathers sponsorship?</CSubject>
		<CBody>NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO
U CAN'T WORK LEGALLY </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q115_C4" CUSERID="U422" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Can i work in qatar under my fathers sponsorship?</CSubject>
		<CBody>thnks </CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q116" QCATEGORY="Cars" QDATE="2011-02-03 01:27:56" QUSERID="U426" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Which car would you recommend? and what options are there?</QSubject>
	<QBody>I'm actually trying arrange a car, and need your advice on which car you consider safe and strong enough but still economically acceptable (affordable safety), also I shouldn't worry too much about regular maintenance and replacing parts and stuff like that?

What options are there: rent, buy, by second hand... and which options would you recommend. I wouldn't buy with an interest bearing loan.

Thank you</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q116_C1" CUSERID="U427" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which car would you recommend? and what options are...</CSubject>
		<CBody>go for toyota. it has a good resale value. if u r ready 2 spend more u an go for a camry or avalon and many more.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q116_C2" CUSERID="U426" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Which car would you recommend? and what options are...</CSubject>
		<CBody>What about Volvo XC90? does it loose value faster than Toyota and Nissan? which is safer?</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q117" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2009-06-13 19:28:57" QUSERID="U428" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>#1 TV News Channel, Why?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Which is your favorite TV news channel, you believe covers news in depth and objectivity? Any admired reporters too?

I have a couple, what about you?

Salam



</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C1" CUSERID="U150" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Super Comedy</CSubject>
		<CBody>Super Comedy</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C2" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Flan....Cool!</CSubject>
		<CBody>You mean this?

http://www.orbit.net/channels.aspx?ch=CO

Best news!
Salam</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C3" CUSERID="U150" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>spot on happy....talk shows</CSubject>
		<CBody>spot on happy....talk shows are just as informative as the "standard" news channels.

thanks for link!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C4" CUSERID="U429" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>TVE</CSubject>
		<CBody>TVE has all what I need, but I don't understand their Spanish sometimes! DW, not bad, and even in English; Al Jazeera is improving tremendously... but let's be honest, all are more or less copying the style of BBC!!
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C5" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I like iReport of CNN. </CSubject>
		<CBody>I like iReport of CNN.

Salam</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C6" CUSERID="U419" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>The Daily Show. My entire</CSubject>
		<CBody>The Daily Show. My entire knowledge comes from John Stewart and his team.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C7" CUSERID="U430" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>FTV???</CSubject>
		<CBody>nah,,, i like BBC...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C8" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Amanpour &amp; Badawi </CSubject>
		<CBody>I have a lot of respect for Christiane Amanpour of the CNN and Zeinab Badawi of the BBC's Hardtalk.

Salam
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C9" CUSERID="U151" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>One more vote for the Daily</CSubject>
		<CBody>One more vote for the Daily Show and Colbert...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C10" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Stewart and Colbert</CSubject>
		<CBody>While I do like to watch Stewart and Colbert's, for their straight critique but they do get on my nerves at times, specially Colberts. 

Salam


</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C11" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>shoeaddict ...Tell you What</CSubject>
		<CBody>FTV and MTV are the best..:)


Salam</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C12" CUSERID="U430" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>yes happy happy</CSubject>
		<CBody>soooo true!!!
love the FW09 collections,specially Ralph Lauren's........</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C13" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>PM...Shoe</CSubject>
		<CBody>Maybe you're right, but I really think he's sometimes overdoing it.

Shoe, you're so serious about this business..:)



Salam


</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C14" CUSERID="U431" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>John Stewart</CSubject>
		<CBody>Did you see his recent interview with Katy Couric (who anchors the CBS Nightly News show).  It's kind of scary when you think that the Daily Show (which I love and do watch daily--at least on the 4 days a week it runs) could be the primary source of news for certain demographics in the US.  I like the PBS News Hours.  It's the only US show that actually covers the days news in depth.  BBC world does a good job.  Fox news is appalling in its slant, especially as it pretends to be objective news (at least MSNBC, which slants in the other direction doesnt pretend to be news instead of opinion).  CNN is OK.  Outside the US and UK, Al Jazeera International really does do a good job of presenting a more third World centered view.  As for Qatar news: fugetaboutit, best source seems to be QL</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C15" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>UkEngQatar ..Very BORING!</CSubject>
		<CBody>Any local channel would have extensive coverage of their leaders' international visits. Egyptian Nile TV covers Mubarak's visits of where he went, who he met with, what he had for lunch, when he played squash, who he shook hands with, and how many steps he climbed up to get back to the plane, en route to Egypt..:)

This is so boring!

Salam



</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C16" CUSERID="U318" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I don't think there is</CSubject>
		<CBody>I don't think there is objectivity in any news channel let alone truthful information...

Even if a certain tv news channel is truthful, it will focus on issues that are of interest to her which does not make things objective. 

However, I would vote for the Arabic Al-Jazeera. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C17" CUSERID="U228" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Huge list.....I don't believe on one channel.....</CSubject>
		<CBody>check many other channels to confirm NEWS (LIKE investigating History) or DISCOVERY Channel....

Personally I feel Al Jazeera show directly from Horse Mouth and don't involve personal commentaries on the subject....

From India most reliable is 
NDTV, TIMES NOW and HEADLINES TODAY...

International NEWS...
BBC, CNN.....

Pakistan
GEO


</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C18" CUSERID="U432" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>love al jazeera</CSubject>
		<CBody>i like al jazeera in arabic, like FOX is a propaganda  machine for U.S right wing AL-Jazeera is a propanganda machine, i never heard about domestic issues of arab world properly in al jazeera . so i love the arabic version escipially the advertisments which is a big relief. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C19" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>lusitano...Authoritarian Channels  Suck!</CSubject>
		<CBody>I was mainly referring to regional channels, don't know about the rest of the world's local news channels. But imagine having to put up with 20 minutes of listing the names of every single member at the leader's reception!

Oh, and of course all internal affairs are good and satisfactory..:)

Salam





</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C20" CUSERID="U95" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>HBO and Star Movies</CSubject>
		<CBody>HBO and Star Movies</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C21" CUSERID="U433" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Happy,
I wonder if the</CSubject>
		<CBody>Happy,
I wonder if the leaders of those countries are that stupid or do they think their people, is?</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C22" CUSERID="U151" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Real news is so depressing.</CSubject>
		<CBody>Real news is so depressing. I stopped watching it a long time ago.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C23" CUSERID="U434" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>...........Dawn News and Al</CSubject>
		<CBody>&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;...........Dawn News and Al Jazeera English..........</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C24" CUSERID="U435" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>The Daily Show &amp; the Colbert</CSubject>
		<CBody>The Daily Show &amp; the Colbert Report.  Without a doubt the most objective news shows in the world. :) </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C25" CUSERID="U419" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Loved last weeks Colbert</CSubject>
		<CBody>Loved last weeks Colbert Report when Obama popped up for the haircut section.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C26" CUSERID="U435" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Loved last nights Daily Show</CSubject>
		<CBody>Loved last nights Daily Show when he compared what was showing on Fox, to what was showing on MSNBC to what was showing on CNN.  I was nearly wetting myself. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C27" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Express News or Geo</CSubject>
		<CBody>Express News or Geo Pakistan......

Or our Pakistani Police,, Cause some times they already knows before the happening of any Incident.LOL</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C28" CUSERID="U249" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>PM I know, I'm just being a smart azz like ususal....</CSubject>
		<CBody>Colbert broadcast from my old stomping grounds last week
Camp Victory iraq...
You can't teach experience...</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C29" CUSERID="U325" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>AlJazeera English!! reached</CSubject>
		<CBody>AlJazeera English!! reached a recorded number of houses around the world in just three years,,,,have a different point for view for everything, &amp; in depth coverage &amp; honest/reliable news which BBC &amp; other channels lack.


~noms~
-----------------------------------------
"Before God we are all equally wise ' and equally foolish" - Albert Einstein

</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C30" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>noms..Was Waiting to Hear "Al-Jazeera" </CSubject>
		<CBody>While I do have high regard for Al-Jazeera English, simply because the Arab world is in dire need for its voice to be heard in main languages, and to balance out international media coverage, but I don't think it's the most objective, no.

Would you agree to that? 

Salam


</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C31" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>PM...Would've Wished for Al-Jazeera</CSubject>
		<CBody>I would've wished for the Al-Jazeera to be the most honest, would've been absolutely proud, but I'm afraid it's not, although it has all the means to become one.

Maybe their policy will change?

Salam





</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C32" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Insha'Allah, Happy Happy</CSubject>
		<CBody>I think they will grow and mature. But if they want to be viewed as anything but an anti-Western mouthpiece they will need watch their editorial bias. Fox doesn't care about such things and is happy to be seen as the Right Wing network it is. I would hope that A-J doesn't follow that same path.

They are positioned (and funded) to make great contributions international media. Unfortunately, as long as they allow someone's politics to color their reporting, they will be marginalized.

I think you get the best sense of what's going on by watching a lot of different news. I watch BBC, CNN, AJE, and MSNBC. I even occasionally Fox so I can see what the enemy is up to :-)
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;#160;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;#160;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;#160;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;I refuse to drink the kool-aid!&lt;/strong&gt; -- &lt;em&gt;PM&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C33" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>PM ...Absolutely Right!</CSubject>
		<CBody>You said it all indeed! specially the last paragraph, I keep thinking what is a 100% objective coverage? There will always be two sides of any story.

I think the BBC is the most objective, but I have to watch CNN and one Arab channel (Al-Jazeera or Al-Arabia) to make sure Im not mislead.


Salam



</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C34" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>PM...Searching for the Truth</CSubject>
		<CBody>But zipping through news channels or their online websites is a very time-consuming procedure, all to dig for where the truth is. I consider this overload by my/today's standards, no time!

Oh, and I'm into news websites polls too..:))

Salam



</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C35" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Curious..Fahmy Alhoweidy is Right</CSubject>
		<CBody>Fahmy Alhoweidy is right, and if this article proves anything, it proves that we're entitled, in Egypt, to criticizing the President's policy without fear. Many people around the world are unaware of this fact.

Not that he is going to act on it!

Salam
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C36" CUSERID="U436" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I like</CSubject>
		<CBody>Al jazeera Eng &amp; Daily Show (John Stewart)
Imran</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C37" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Curious and Ash... Me too</CSubject>
		<CBody>I'm sure I'm very unaware of many things in life. This is why objectivity is at risk, always.

Ash, I'm sure there is worse, you just don't know about it...:)

Salam 

 
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C38" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>The late or Tonight Show? </CSubject>
		<CBody>Anyone watches David Letterman and Jay Leno? 

And how come no one here shared who their favorite news reporter/anchor was?

Salam


</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C39" CUSERID="U433" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>HH,
Leno has recently been</CSubject>
		<CBody>HH,
Leno has recently been replaced by Connan O Brien.
Although these talk shows host have a good sense of humor, not all the jokes are tailor made for an international crowd. Sometimes they are just too local and little or no interest to international audiences... just some times :)

As for reporters/news anchors, CNN has a few very good ones; Christiane Amanpour is an example among others.


The news anchor in Dubai One, sound like bad acting!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C40" CUSERID="U433" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I would also go for Daily</CSubject>
		<CBody>I would also go for Daily Show.
By the way, can anybody tell me at what time and day its on, here in Doha?
thanks
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C41" CUSERID="U435" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>It's on at 9:00 pm on</CSubject>
		<CBody>It's on at 9:00 pm on Showtime. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C42" CUSERID="U433" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Thanks Gipsy!
I used to</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks Gipsy!
I used to watch it on CNN, sat at 17:30 but they stopped it since a couple of weeks ago!
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C43" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Counting Votes Like Dracula..:)</CSubject>
		<CBody>It seems that I should start counting votes, like QL's Dracula masters on most of his threads.

Daily Show and Colbert Report are way ahead so far!

Salam
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C44" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Qatar TV is the only TV</CSubject>
		<CBody>Qatar TV is the only TV station which doesn't spill lies. And most importantly, we are informed about the numbers of letters (not the content, though)the Emir and his son have sent and received during the day.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C45" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>MagicDragon...Qatar TV's Aldar Talk Show</CSubject>
		<CBody>Qatar TV has a very good talk show, titled Aldar , which tackles and highlights very important local issues, and puts it out to the public. I'm sure there are other shows I'm not aware of. 

Also Good Morning Qatar is a good Radio broadcast, not only seeking entertaining but reform.

salam</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C46" CUSERID="U437" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>.</CSubject>
		<CBody>&lt;i&gt;1. BBC Documentaries [All time favourite]
2. CNN&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/atifsimi/3624627272/" title="T20 WC09 by atif.simi, on Flickr"&gt;&lt;img src="http://farm4.static.flickr.com/3321/3624627272_8f0347f6e7_o.jpg" width="440" height="65" alt="T20 WC09" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C47" CUSERID="U433" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Happy,
Hopefully the</CSubject>
		<CBody>Happy,
Hopefully the situation improves soon in these authoritarian regimes!
At least in countries like Egypt, Tunisia and others, the people are aware and active but some like the one we are at the moment, total submission and passivity rules!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C48" CUSERID="U318" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>it is better to disable to</CSubject>
		<CBody>it is better to disable to sound sometimes otherwise, like bleu said, you may hear inappropriate terms. 

I am referring here to what the courteous G. W. Bush once said about Syria speaking to T. Blaire over lunch!</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C49" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>I bet, that's what's</CSubject>
		<CBody>I bet, that's what's happening, bleu.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C50" CUSERID="U428" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Curious..Ouch!!</CSubject>
		<CBody>And let me add to your point about objectivity that in today's world, news coverage has to be 3D, the old myth of 2 sides of the story isn't enough any more, there is always a 3rd party involved, then 3D it shall be..:) 

Salam


</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C51" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>That music is hilarious!</CSubject>
		<CBody>It's so cheery and really compliments the Emir's wonderful smile :-)

&lt;p&gt;
&amp;#160;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;#160;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&amp;#160;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;I refuse to drink the kool-aid!&lt;/strong&gt; -- &lt;em&gt;PM&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q117_C52" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>BBC</CSubject>
		<CBody>BBC</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q118" QCATEGORY="Salary and Allowances" QDATE="2008-11-19 14:35:58" QUSERID="U438" QTYPE="YES_NO" QGOLD_YN="Unsure">
	<QSubject>urgent plz: is this a good offer?</QSubject>
	<QBody>my offer is basic salry 1500 usd, a car and the housing are on the own of te company (not shared housing).The job is a kind of management position, nationality lebanese. Thx by advance to all</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q118_C1" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Unsure">
		<CSubject>qatarisun - it is the</CSubject>
		<CBody>qatarisun - it is the reality. I earn QR 6000 on the same capacity. I am Asian :)

Ban Spoon Feeding not Me
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q118_C2" CUSERID="U439" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Unsure">
		<CSubject>I work for the government</CSubject>
		<CBody>I work for the government and all my Qatari counterparts make the same as I do.... in all the departments based on grade and we are more than 1000 employees. Private companies may differ but anything on a grade all the salaries are the same or within a specific range. Only difference is the social allowance, which I dont get but as they are Qataris they dont get housing.... With my housing allowance I actually make more than my Qatari counterparts. 

As for their inflated titles, thats a different story. I have a person in a position above me who gets to sit and read the paper all day and make double my salary... thats something different all togther. 

_______________________________________________________
"Diplomacy is the art of saying 'Nice doggie' until you can find a rock - Will Rogers"</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q118_C3" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Default Nick - I will insert</CSubject>
		<CBody>Default Nick - I will insert that in My C.V. :)

Ban Spoon Feeding not Me
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q118_C4" CUSERID="U112" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>charan, i am aware of your</CSubject>
		<CBody>charan, i am aware of your heartbreaking story.. i also recall, you menationed once that your tea boy gets some twice as much as you do...
by the way, charan, what happened to your pretty-sweety wifie? did she leave you eventually?? :)


&lt;i&gt; &lt;b&gt;
*********************
You become responsible forever for what you have tamed. Antoine de Saint-Exupry &lt;/b&gt; &lt;/i&gt; 

&lt;img src="http://cdnll.img1.imagechef.com/w/080610/anmd46ebbf9c8c024ef.gif"&gt;


</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q118_C5" CUSERID="U37" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>qatarisun - We are very</CSubject>
		<CBody>qatarisun - We are very unfortunate souls not like you who can afford Admirals 2-4 times a week.

She left on 17 oct &amp; came back on 10 Nov :(

Ban Spoon Feeding not Me
</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q118_C6" CUSERID="U439" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Eagle, perhaps you do not</CSubject>
		<CBody>Eagle, perhaps you do not understand what Qatarisun and I are saying.... they are grades above us but are not qualified to be there, has nothing with "being informed about the world in order to be able to lead company in strategic directions / way forward"... 
_______________________________________________________
"Diplomacy is the art of saying 'Nice doggie' until you can find a rock - Will Rogers"</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q119" QCATEGORY="Qatar Living Lounge" QDATE="2010-02-25 13:47:47" QUSERID="U440" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>have it or don't leave the house at all</QSubject>
	<QBody>What are the things you must do or have before leaving your house?? </QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q119_C1" CUSERID="U440" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>i'll start.. morning</CSubject>
		<CBody>i'll start.. morning shower,wallet and clothes.. lol


~Welcome Sunshine~</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q119_C2" CUSERID="U441" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>for me...</CSubject>
		<CBody>clothes,slippers,MP4 player and my eye-liner ;-)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q119_C3" CUSERID="U440" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>breakfast is the most</CSubject>
		<CBody>breakfast is the most important meal but i don't take breakfast.. :(

~Welcome Sunshine~</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q119_C4" CUSERID="U441" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>so do i,Visper....</CSubject>
		<CBody>so do i,Visper....</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q119_C5" CUSERID="U441" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Visper</CSubject>
		<CBody>i take my car keys and wallet(coz it has my license in it) only when i'm driving by myself.otherwise,i don't think it's necessary for me to carry cash or my mobile or my car keys :-)</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q120" QCATEGORY="Life in Qatar" QDATE="2009-02-08 09:07:52" QUSERID="U12" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Where to get England Scoccer kit for Kids...</QSubject>
	<QBody>Hi does any of you know where I could get an England  football kit for kids.. Checked all sports shop in City Centre and Olympic sports near crazy signal no luck. If you have see kids size kit please let me know.. Will try Villagio this afternoon..

Thanks</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q120_C1" CUSERID="U442" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where to get England Scoccer kit for Kids...</CSubject>
		<CBody>You can also try City Center.

They have many sports shops next to each other. 

The good thing about english fans, is that they keep hoping that their team will actually win something....</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q120_C2" CUSERID="U12" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where to get England Scoccer kit for Kids...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Bundle of Thanks Biddy lou, After disappointed trips to city Centre and Villagio managed to get the Kit from Golden Sports as you suggested..

Thanks</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q120_C3" CUSERID="U443" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where to get England Scoccer kit for Kids...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Your welcome, just hope it was LEEDS UNITED that yo got lol</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q120_C4" CUSERID="U444" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where to get England Scoccer kit for Kids...</CSubject>
		<CBody>GO SPORT  in villagio all kind of clubs  </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q120_C5" CUSERID="U12" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where to get England Scoccer kit for Kids...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks qatarhero, planning to go there this evening..</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q120_C6" CUSERID="U443" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where to get England Scoccer kit for Kids...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Have seen footy strips for kids in sports shop, opposite Doha Clinic on Al Merqab Street.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q120_C7" CUSERID="U443" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where to get England Scoccer kit for Kids...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yes, there was strips for kids, last time I was in there. But that was about 6 mths ago Maybe worth having a look. </CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q120_C8" CUSERID="U12" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Where to get England Scoccer kit for Kids...</CSubject>
		<CBody>Thanks Biddy lou..will try that shop also..</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q121" QCATEGORY="Computers and Internet" QDATE="2008-12-14 17:07:55" QUSERID="U445" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Recall sent msg?</QSubject>
	<QBody>Is there any chance to recall sent message using Gmail?
If possible how?

Thanks advance</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q121_C1" CUSERID="U151" CGOLD="Potential" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>RE: Recall sent msg?</CSubject>
		<CBody>There's no way to recall any sent message in any system.

Any email, mobile, IM, or even personal contact ...</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>

<Question QID="Q122" QCATEGORY="Doha Shopping" QDATE="2011-12-03 16:41:00" QUSERID="U446" QTYPE="GENERAL" QGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
	<QSubject>Spray snow</QSubject>
	<QBody>Does anyone know where to get snow in a can from?  I don't mean the foam spray that most places seem to sell - the more powder type stuff that you can spray on the window!

Thanks in advance!

Ellie
xxx</QBody>
	<Comment CID="Q122_C1" CUSERID="U447" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Christmas and New year aren't</CSubject>
		<CBody>Christmas and New year aren't really celebrated over here. You will find some decorations and artificial trees but they go very quickly!   As for New Year,going to bed at the normal time is the best you can do!  We stayed up for one but were so far ahead,time wise,to ring up family back home that  we gave up.Had a glass of bubbly and that was that!  I guess,if you have lots of like minded friends,you can get together for a 'do'.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q122_C2" CUSERID="U448" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>They sell it in Carrefour</CSubject>
		<CBody>They sell it in Carrefour (City Centre) along with a load of other Christmas Tat.  Not sure if it's the type you want though, you'd have to go down and check.</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q122_C3" CUSERID="U443" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>have you tried the party shop</CSubject>
		<CBody>have you tried the party shop next to hallmark card shop in villagio, bet they will have it</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q122_C4" CUSERID="U449" CGOLD="Good" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>Yeah, party shop got the</CSubject>
		<CBody>Yeah, party shop got the powdery snow spray. I bought some yesterday :)</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q122_C5" CUSERID="U446" CGOLD="Dialogue" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>OOOh tank you guys - I had</CSubject>
		<CBody>OOOh tank you guys - I had tried that party shop about a week ago but at the time they didn't have any in - they said they may get some - but you know, wasn't sure whether to believe them or not lol!!!  So that's me off to Villagio this week - SNOW IN A CAN! :-)
xxx</CBody>
	</Comment>
	<Comment CID="Q122_C6" CUSERID="U202" CGOLD="Bad" CGOLD_YN="Not Applicable">
		<CSubject>that's x-mas,</CSubject>
		<CBody>pure business!</CBody>
	</Comment>
</Question>